Summer break began.
The students headed home.
When I said I was going to stay at the dorm,
Sarasa invited me to stay with her.
I'm going to stay with a friend over summer break.
It's really like... what friends do!
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone yet
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"The Platform and the Silver Bridge"
How can I make her feel better?
Wait, girls always get excited
talking about their boyfriends, right?
Hey, what's your boyfriend like, Sarasa?
His name's Akiya, and he's training to be a kabuki actor.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
She didn't get excited at all.
But I'm sorry, Watanabe.
If you don't change, you'll never be
a top star of the Kouka revue.
You weren't playing Tybalt.
You were playing Satomi Sei's Tybalt.
It was a perfect copy of her performance.
That's why it was so good.
But copying doesn't get you success
in the Kouka revue's star system.
Everything on that stage is built
to make their top stars shine.
They don't want a traced-over copy
of already-existing stars.
They want something totally new.
They want you, Watanabe Sarasa.
And there wasn't any of you in that Tybalt.
Sarasa?
Sorry, did you say something?
I was totally lost in thought.
Thinking about what Mr. Andou said?
Yeah.
For a guy who looks like he doesn't
brush his hair, he sure is harsh.
Don't make fun of his hair!
He's actually pretty sensitive
about his curly hair.
Wait, you're the—
The top stars of the Winter Troupe!
I wanted to be a Female Lead,
but ended up growing seven centimeters
in my first year at Kouka.
You even threatened to drop out
if you couldn't play Female Lead.
Really?
But the Phantom encouraged me to stay,
so I agreed to play Male Lead
Are you two headed to Tokyo, too?
Yes, we're visiting home.
Great.
We're headed to a meeting to discuss
my debut performance as Winter's top star.
We're doing The Phantom of the Opera.
Random question, why do we call Mr. Andou the Phantom?
You don't know?
Mr. Andou was a popular actor
in the Japanese musical troupe "Sou."
And he was best known for playing
the Phantom in Phantom of the Opera.
I was a huge fan of his.
I had a huge crush on him, too.
But he hurt himself in an accident
when he fell into the orchestra pit,
so he had to retire from acting.
It crushed him.
He lives and breathes acting.
I think that's why he came to teach at Kouka,
to do whatever he could
to stay in the theater world.
"My acting teacher said my performance
was just a copy of another top star.
Apparently copying is okay in kabuki,
but not here."
"I'm so Sara-sad..."
Great Great Master is so cool!
Sarasa, that's Master Kaou,
but he's not the real Master Kaou.
Huh? Really, Akiya?
Is that true, Great Master?
It sure is.
Every kabuki performer learns to
perfectly copy the previous generation.
When they act, they bring those
centuries-old performers back to life.
Back to life...?
"August Kabuki Series"
"Shirakawa Akiya"
Shirakawa Akiya... that's Sarasa's boyfriend.
Ai! Sorry that took so long!
I'm home, Grandpa!
You're early! I got you your favorite doll cakes.
Grandpa, this is my roommate
I'm always going on about, Ai!
We're best friends!
Best friends?
Th-These are for you.
I don't know if these suit your taste.
How very kind of you.
Come now, no need to sit so formally.
No, I insist.
I'm her best friend. I have to make a good impression!
Oh, hey, Sarasa, you got someone upstairs—
Hey! How've you been, Sarasa?
Welcome back, Sarasa!
Shou, Keiko! It's great to see you!
Welcome back!
Sarasa, you had any of that Kobe beef yet?
Mr. Kuma!
Didja get even taller?
Did I?
When's your big debut?
C'mon, now, she's got a while to go for that!
Finally, some peace and quiet.
Sorry about that, Ai.
I didn't mean to ignore you.
It's okay.
I can't feel my legs anymore.
Ai, I've gotta go tell my grandma I'm back in Asakusa.
Do you mind if I step out for 20 minutes?
Go ahead.
I can't even move.
My cat Nono should be upstairs!
You can go play with her if you're bored.
Okay.
If I can get up there.
What? JPX?
Shirakawa Akiya.
Huh? What?
Are you Sarasa's boyfriend?
What?
This is the first time we're speaking, right?
You can't just start off with that.
I don't care how famous you are,
it's called having manners!
I'm sorry. I'm not really good with people.
And Sarasa's the first friend
I've ever had. I was just curious.
I'm really sorry.
We've been friends since we were kids.
We took traditional dance lessons together.
You'll have to hear the rest from Sarasa.
I'm back, Grandma.
Someone said those words to me again.
If you don't change, you'll never be
a top star of the Kouka revue.
It will never happen! Not ever!
No way in the world will you ever
be able to play Sukeroku!
The word "never" always makes me feel horrible.
"Never" is a curse.
Hi, Ms. Tomoe!
Sarasa was two years younger than me.
Her family ran a tatami shop,
and she was always bright and cheerful.
Whenever she came for her lesson...
Mind if I watch, Ms. Tomoe?
Kouzaburou always came to see her for some reason.
Hey, Sarasa. Long time no see.
What's this? We're in the middle of Akiya's lesson.
Kouzaburou is married to
the only daughter of Shirakawa Kaou,
15th of his name, national treasure
and head of the Satomi house and troupe.
Ms. Tomoe is Master Kaou's younger sister.
My father is Master Kaou's cousin.
He used to be a kabuki actor,
but gave up and quit early in his career.
I was born into this big kabuki family.
So what're you learning, Akiya?
Yakko.
Ooh, I wanna do Yakko, too!
Can I do it, too, Ms. Tomoe?
Sure.
Master Kaou?
Great Great Master's here, too!
Can I watch you two dance?
Huh?
Okay.
I started training to perform kabuki
this year, when I was eight.
The kabuki world values bloodline,
which meant that I was the most likely
person to become the 16th Shirakawa Kaou.
However...
Akiya! Are you okay?!
Did you hit your head?
S-Sorry, I'm okay.
Are you okay, Akiya?
Yeah. Sorry for messing up, Sarasa—
I always knew you had good balance,
but my goodness.
I heard Master Kaou came to watch you dance today.
Was that girl there, too?
You mean Sarasa? Yeah, she was there.
We are friends.
Is that right?
She's really good at dancing.
She's super strong, and has good balance—
Sure, but she's a girl.
My mom had noticed it, too,
but I pretended not to.
I had to.
Akiya! A newbie like you's only here
'cause you're kinda related to Master Kaou!
If Kouzaburou has a boy,
they'll throw you right into the trash!
What?
I'm the only kid who can perform today?
Yeah, all the other kids
came down with a bad flu.
I have to go out there by myself?
You'll be fine, Akiya.
Thank you so much for inviting us today.
Um...
What's wrong, Akiya?
But I have lines.
If it's just me, then it won't be like we practiced.
What if I mess up?
Akiya, you need to have more confidence.
The acting world won't go easy on you
just because you're a kid.
You'd better get it together.
I know, but...
It's okay, Akiya!
Whenever we played pretend kabuki,
you didn't mess up, not even once!
Master Kaou,
we need more than one child for Agemaki,
or the procession will look off.
Could we have Sarasa stand in?
She and I have watched the Sukeroku DVD
together plenty of times at Tomoe's.
She's memorized all the lines.
Very well.
Come here.
Okay!
Look, Akiya, we match!
Here, take this.
Take a sniff. Doesn't that smell good?
Do you feel a little better now?
Oh, y-yes.
It'll be your lucky charm.
I can have it?
Sarasa thinks it's so cool that a kid
your age gets to perform in kabuki shows.
She's so very proud of you.
We're going to walk out onto the stage from there.
Just do what Akiya does, and look straight ahead.
Close your mouth.
No one had taught her how to steel her gaze like that.
She faced forward towards the audience,
as if doing exactly that was as natural as breathing.
As if she was born with something I didn't have.
That girl was something else.
You know they say she's Kouzaburou's illegitimate daughter.
How sad.
If she'd been born a boy, she could've
been next in line for the Kaou name.
She's Kouzaburou's daughter?
And if she'd been born a boy, then I...
Akiya?
Oh. Hello, ma'am.
I heard you made quite the effort at the last performance.
Master Kaou was very proud.
He was?
Akiya! I had my lesson before you today!
Oh, hey.
I'm gonna go see a movie with Grandpa Ken today!
See you later!
Sarasa got to perform with me.
Huh? So she played the second child?
She did really good, even though it was her first time.
Someone even said that if she'd been
born a boy, she could be the next Kaou.
That's how good she was.
I knew I shouldn't have said it.
I knew what I was doing.
But I was a child, and had no idea that throwing a pebble in the pond would ripple out that far.
Don't be stupid!
It doesn't matter how good you are,
or how much natural talent you possess!
It will never happen! Not ever!
No way in the world will you ever
be able to play Sukeroku!
Now, go. Leave!
Go home!
The next day, Sarasa stopped coming for dance classes.
Then...
Cut the bullcrap!
We did not bring Sarasa here so she could
get traumatized by the lot of you!
We are done with you!
She's our little girl.
Find yourself another tatami shop!
Kouzaburou kept his head bowed the entire time.
You're the kabuki boy who's friends with Sarasa.
Sorry about all that yelling.
Didn't mean to scare ya.
Sarasa won't come here anymore.
But I'm only cuttin' her off from kabuki.
I hope you'll still keep bein' friends with her.
I-I...
Near the end of summer,
Sarasa's grandmother passed away.
"Funeral"
We weren't allowed to come to the funeral,
but Master Kaou insisted we
pay our respects from a distance.
Sarasa...
Master Kaou, it's...
It's all my fault.
Don't say that, Akiya.
Hold onto that feeling.
It'll make you a better actor.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's a little late, but here. Happy birthday.
The Last Burst Premier Skeleton Taku from Floor Kings!
You can see-through.
Thank you so much, Akiya!
You sure it isn't a defect piece?
I've got one more present for you.
"August Kabuki Series"
Sukeroku...
I'm playing Taura Tomimatsu.
Kouzaburou is playing Fukuyama Katsugi.
And Master Kaou is, of course, playing Sukeroku.
Thanks, but I'm not allowed to see kabuki shows.
I asked Grandpa Ken and he said it was okay.
I have two tickets, so take Narata, too.
Sarasa, you know that thing
you asked for advice for on Twitter?
Oh, yeah.
Kabuki typically involves the perfect
replication of famous performances,
but it's not all replication.
Huh?
Sukeroku's a superhero story, built around
a cool guy getting his revenge.
But you also get to see him
being helpless and compassionate.
That was all new to the audiences
in the Edo period, and they ate it up.
Even now, they're still trying
new things in kabuki.
Half-finished plays by famous playwrights
are being adapted into new shows.
I stopped doing kabuki when I was six, so I had no idea.
As we try these new things,
we need to maintain our old traditions,
while also entertaining our audience,
as we have for centuries.
Us actors need to have the dedication
to fulfilling those expectations.
Dedication...
I want to show you my dedication, Sarasa.
Akiya...
Oh, I've gotta head out.
Sarasa, I'm not scared to go out on stage anymore.
"August Kabuki Series"
Hey, how are you connected
to all this kabuki stuff?
Oh, when I was six, I got to
perform in Sukeroku, just once.
Even though you're a girl?
Little girls are allowed to perform in kabuki.
I got to walk across the platform with Akiya.
What was it like?
It was quiet.
I felt the audience's gaze like heat on my skin.
We may have been in the same room,
but up on stage, it was like being in a different world.
I felt as if I'd transformed into someone else.
But I don't know. I think I'm still...
I want to go see the play.
Huh?
Take me to see the kabuki play.
Look, it's Sukeroku's 'The Entrance.'
I'm so good at it!
Yes, you sure are.
When I grow up, I'm gonna be Sukeroku!
Wow. I wish I could see that.
I didn't know if her tears were because of fond memories or something else entirely.
I just hope she doesn't regret coming tonight.
Did you have a fun summer break?
Yeah! Thanks for seeing us off.
I'll see you soon.
Winter break isn't that soon, though.
Are you going to come with her then, Narata?
Probably.
I'm gonna go grab some lunch.
Sarasa, y'know,
when you know what you want,
all you can do is move towards it.
We've only just started down our paths. So it's okay.
Even if we lose sight of what we want sometimes.
It happens to you, too?
All the time, even when I was little.
But I always decide to keep going.
After all, there's only one path to follow.
I want to play Lady Oscar.
Right.
Please play Sukeroku, Akiya.
They're shaking hands? Aren't they dating?
I'll keep walking on the path that glows white in the darkness
A long, narrow path that can only be walked alone
I walk forward so that I won't fall behind other people's shadows
If I just head straight forward, it'll appear right in front of me
Now, let's open the door
There are sparkling stars in this vast sky
If just I had wings,
I'd flap and flutter high through the space like a bird
Going around the constellations, and pursuing the stars
we had just started this endless journey
"Act 8: Kaoru's Summer"