Ta-dah!
Ai, look, look!
Check it out! This is the Kouka uniform!
I know. I have one, too.
Guidance Week and the entrance ceremony
are finally behind us,
and tomorrow, we get to start classes!
She was so excited last night.
I'll at least try to
wake her up this time.
Wake up.
Well, she's not waking up. I tried.
Good morning, Narata.
Good morning, Sugimoto.
Where is our troublesome Watanabe?
She wouldn't wake up.
Excuse me, I'll be entering your room!
Watanabe! Watanabe!
Come on, Watanabe!
Watanabe Sarasa!
Wake up!
You can not be late
on your very first day!
Get ready at once and come
to the auditorium!
O-Okay!
Wait, it's only 5:30.
Do we have
exercises with the JSDF again?
No. We're meeting people who are
much scarier than the JSDF.
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone right now
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"Those Who Long to
Cross the Silver Bridge"
Good morning! I am the first-year
student representative, Sugimoto Sawa.
We're very sorry we're late!
Don't worry, you're not late.
There's still five minutes till 6.
Our centennial class is so diligent!
Who are these lovely ladies?
Those are the second-year students,
the 99th Kouka Class.
Keep quiet!
Sugimoto Sawa.
I see you are representing your class.
Thank you.
The faculty told me the highest
exam scorer earns that privilege.
I'll do my best.
Good morning, first-years.
I'm the second-year representative,
Takei Tomomi.
Today, in accordance
with school tradition,
we will show you the ropes
for morning cleaning.
Thank you for your time!
--Thank you!
I'll be a top star!
It's our pleasure.
Each first-year has been assigned
a second-year student advisor.
They will support you and give you advice
throughout your next year here.
Excuse me, who's my advisor?
There she goes, how annoying.
Depending upon your advisor,
your life here can be a living hell.
Sheesh, Risa, you're scary.
Now, when your names are called,
please go to the cleaning location with your advisor.
"Japanese Room"
I'll be your advisor.
I'm Nojima Hijiri, vice-president of
the second-year class.
It's so good to meet you!
It's nice to meet you, too.
Your eyelashes are so long,
and your skin is so fair!
No wonder you got to be in JPX!
Thanks.
Everyone was fighting over
who got to be your advisor.
We did rock-paper-scissors
for it, and I won!
I felt like I'd been chosen
to be the center for JPX!
I see.
Are you not a morning person?
Or have you low blood pressure?
Neither.
I'm a huge JPX fan.
If I hadn't gotten into Kouka,
I might've auditioned for them!
I mean, everyone in JPX is so cute and
lively, with their big, sparkling smiles!
That's why I'm so honored
to be your advisor for the next...
You weren't one of my fans, then.
Huh?
You start sweeping from
one side of the room.
And don't whack it on the ground.
Okay. I've never cleaned a room before.
I can tell.
So why do you think
I wasn't one of your fans?
Because I'm not lively and
I don't have a big, sparkling smile.
I'm guessing you're a fan
of Kozono Momo.
W-Well, I liked you, too!
Your whole 'not smiling' thing
made you this cool-headed beauty!
Don't worry, I don't mind.
So you probably wish to play
Female Lead, I suppose?
Not really.
You mean?
I don't have any specific wish.
Really?
Well, I think you'll be glad
you got me as your advisor.
Some second-years are going to be
really mean to their first-years.
The competition starts
long before you get into the Troupe.
It started the moment
you got into this school.
But I don't think you'll have to
worry about it, Narata.
C'mon, silly!
This is how you use a broom.
Keep your hands apart,
and place your dominant hand here.
I'm Nakayama Risa,
and I'll be your student advisor.
Yay, my advisor's a Latin beauty
with a rockin' bod!
And I hate when people point that out.
You'll be cleaning this traditional dance classroom
for next two hours before class.
First, sweep the floor.
After that, prick the dirt off the floor using pin
and wipe them.
Brush off the dust from the window frames.
And don't leave a single stain on the mirror.
I have two hours to do
that all by myself?!
Don't like it?
I'll do my best!
This is taking forever.
It better not, or you'll be late to class.
That'd be a big problem!
How tall are you?
I'm 178 centimeters tall!
And your age?
Fifteen!
I got in when I was in 12th grade,
so I'm 19. I'll be 20 next year.
It sucks.
Why? You're brimming with
mature ladylike energy!
Cut the chatter.
Okay!
It's just that I really like
talking with you, Risa!
Well, I don't in the least.
Then I'll find something
you'll like talking about!
Don't bother.
Figured! I'd better focus on this
cleaning, or it really will take forever!
You wanna be Oscar, huh?
Yes! I came to this school so I could
learn how to play Lady Os-
Well, you won't.
Huh?
You'll never play Oscar.
It will never happen! Not ever!
It doesn't matter how good you are,
or how much natural talent you possess!
No way in the world will you ever
be able to play Sukeroku!
Watanabe?
Watanabe, you okay?
Hey, Watanabe!
Why? Why can't I be Lady Oscar?
Look, stop crying!
They're gonna think I'm bullying you!
She's too tall to play Lady Oscar, after all.
The actress playing André
would have to be taller than her,
Why can't I play her?
and it's impossible.
Also, none of us wanted
to be your advisor.
Sticking out like a sore thumb
is fatal in this women world.
If I told her that, though,
how badly would she react?
Wow, so you want to be
a top Female Lead, too, Risa!
Shh! Don't tell anyone yet, Hijiri!
I'm still kinda shy about it.
They're gonna say
it doesn't fit my personality.
I don't think that's true!
You're gorgeous, Risa, and you're one of
the best singers and dancers we have.
Y-You think so?
But your voice and look might not fit a Female Lead.
Y'know, you'd be way better off
playing older women as a Woman Lead!
Huh?
'Cause you're so sexy!
But you're not exactly sweet nor
tidy-looking, you know?
You'd be perfect playing Jeanne,
or Carlotta, or Kurotokage!
Evil villainess roles would be perfect for you.
Man, though, if you were
just a little taller,
being a top Male Lead
wouldn't be just a dream for you!
That was the day I learned
that only girls like Hijiri
had a chance of becoming
a top Female Lead.
Girls with angelic faces, strong
determination, and a mean streak.
Why can't I play Lady Oscar?
Um...
I know! You stood under the cherry tree
before the welcome ceremony, right?
Right.
"Noone who stood the Kouka
cherry tree before admission,
"has never become a
Kouka top star in past 100 years."
That's the tree's curse.
That's it?
Yep.
Then I'm gonna break that curse.
I couldn't be here if I was a guy,
but I was lucky enough to be born a girl,
and I got picked to study here!
There's no such thing as absolutes
when it comes to can or can't!
I'm not gonna let such
meaningless curse hold me back!
I see.
'Cause nobody knows
what you're capable of?
Do your best.
I will!
I will, too.
It's almost time for class.
Let's hurry.
I'll give you a special assistance today.
How nice!
"First-Year Lockers"
I'm here!
Watanabe! I was starting to worry!
Here I thought you'd messed up again.
Why?
If one of us first-years messes up,
we all get punished for it.
The second-years will yell at all of us.
Your advisor seemed kinda strict,
so hopefully that means you did okay?
Yep! Risa doesn't mince words,
but she's really nice!
She definitely messed up!
Our advisors were
scary, too, right, Chika?
She stared daggers at me when I
dropped the broom earlier, Chiaki!
Kouka activites are really intense, huh?
But your advisor looked
really nice, Narata!
I'm not sure.
How was our Lady Oscar?
Nothing special. She's still a child.
My, what's wrong, Risa? You look happy!
You must have it rough, Hijiri.
People think Naracchi could be
a top Female Lead one day.
I'm not sure what you're implying,
but you're definitely mistaken.
Naracchi has zero motivation
for Kouka, after all.
Well, you never know what wind
will lift her sails in the future.
"Sarasa: First class is ballet.
Wearing a leotard makes me feel so girly.
Everyone is so good at ballet, too."
"Jiraiya: Kabuki practice all day today."
What do you want, Kouzaburou?
Those are Sarasa's tweets,
right? Lemme see.
I need to make sure you and Sarasa
are keeping it wholesome.
That's none of your business!
Remind me, Akiya,
who bought that tablet for you?
Ooh, a cool Latin senior advisor taught her
how to clean a classroom today.
Even I haven't read that far yet.
Wipe that look off your face, Akiya.
Your biggest fans are older women.
No rude looks, or you'll lose them all.
"Sarasa: A cool Latin beauty
taught me how to clean a classroom."
Sarasa-san's 15, too?
She must be getting big.
She is. She's already taller than me.
Wow.
She was so tiny when she was
taking dance lessons with you here.
I wish we could've kept her around.
But she's in Kobe now.
Maybe I'll go sneak a peek at her.
Don't be a creepy stalker.
By the way, Akiya.
Yeah?
Coming to you is getting annoying.
Could you give me the password
for this account?
I'm Andou, your acting teacher.
So I'd planned on talking about
Shakespearean dramas today,
but change of plans:
Today, we'll introduce
ourselves to the class.
Mr. Andou.
I don't think we should waste our
important class time on self-introductions.
Well then, I'll start with the introductions!
Hold on, now.
You all know
this is no normal school.
When you graduate from a high school,
you'd normally go on to college, find a job,
take an apprenticeship, get married, etc.
But here, you've got but two options:
Sink or swim. Continue or drop.
When you graduate,
you'll join the Kouka Troupe.
That means you're stuck together forever.
It'd be a good idea for you
to learn more about one another
so that you can make your
life together here easier even just a little.
Very well, Mr. Andou.
Then, as our class representative, I will go first.
There goes Miss Bossypants.
I'm Sugimoto Sawa, and I'm 16.
My family runs a ballet studio in Tokyo,
where I studied ballet from a young age.
Though going abroad was in the topic,
but since I want to
perform musical theater,
so I applied to the Kouka School of
Musical and Theatrical Arts.
I'm honored to be here.
I'm Hoshino Kaoru, and I'm 18.
My mom and grandmother were both
Spring Troupe Female Leads.
But because I've got this great height,
I intend to play Male Lead.
I'd like to add that
I want to be an Male Lead as well!
All right, now.
I'm Sawada Chiaki!
And I'm Sawada Chika!
Chika got in last year, but I didn't.
So I waited a year so we could
both get in together!
Um, I'm Yamada Ayako.
I've loved Kouka ever since I was little.
I can't believe I actually got in...
A-Anyway, I'm going to give my all!
I'm Watanabe Sarasa, and I'm 15!
I've always dreamed of
playing Lady Oscar.
Yes, we know,
you're going to be a top star, right?
Right! I love anime, manga,
and period pieces,
and I live in Asakusa in Tokyo with my
Grandpa Ken, who makes tatami mats!
Oh, and we have a cat named Nono!
Nono's nose is always twitching-
Tell us more about your cat later.
All right, last one.
I'm Narata Ai. I'm 16.
I've done ballet since I was little.
I was taught by my uncle, Narata Taichi,
who's a ballet teacher here.
That's all.
Really? You know there's more.
My mother is an
actress, Narata Kimiko.
I was in JPX48 and was
13th in the election.
After that, I quit...
They made me quit,
so I came here. That's all.
Wow, you were a JPX idol, Ai?!
I had no idea-
Well, that's that.
Let's head out for our tour
of the Kouka Theatre's backstage.
Huh?!
Backstage!
I got permission to take you on
a tour from two to three today.
You'll see that the stage doesn't
belong to just its actresses.
What a wonderful surprise!
First, we have the costuming department.
The embellishments are all
hand-sewn! Oh, wow!
I know those gigantic feathers!
Those are worn by the top Male Lead
of the Winter Troupe, like Kazahana Sou!
They're too incredible to look at.
My eyes!
The bunny girl costume!
Wow! Look at this mountain of dresses!
It's just like Rose Bertin!
I feel like Rosalie!
"Rose what?"
Right, Ai?
Okay, let's move on.
What do we say, everyone?
Thank you for having us!
I saw Naracchi!
She might try to lie low, but she still stands out.
I'll have to brag to my son.
Did you see that other stand-out girl?
The one with the twinkling eyes
and the towering height.
The set department is just right behind the stage.
That's a design.
That's a long brush!
I've never seen one like that.
Whoa, it's all Styrofoam!
But it looks so real!
You think so?
C'mon, Watanabe, don't get in their way.
It's all good, Mr. Andou.
Gettin' praise from future actresses
gets us all motivated to work harder.
Great! I'm gonna be a top star one day,
I hope you'll make
an awesome set for me then!
There she goes again.
Well, all right! No goin' back
on a bold statement like that.
We'll be waitin' for ya then!
Yep! We got ourselves a deal!
Thank you for your time!
Hey, you idiot! Watanabe!
Don't go through there!
Watanabe!
That's the stage!
Watanabe! Get back here, right now!
And don't you dare walk out
on the Silver Bridge!
The Silver Bridge?
The Silver Bridge is the most
prominent part of the stage.
Only Kouka's most dazzling stars
can cross that bridge.
Yeah, only the top Male Lead and
Female Lead and a handful of others.
That's what we all aim for.
The Silver Bridge.
Someone's out on the stage.
Judging from height, it's probably Yama.
Pop a light on him.
To become one of Kouka's top stars,
you need hard work,
talent, star quality,
and enough luck to be
given the right chance.
Watanabe Sarasa's stage presence
was dazzling.
"Ex-JPX idol Ai Narata
enrolls in Kouka School!"
I'm finally here in Kobe.
I'll keep walking on the path
that glows white in the darkness
A long, narrow path
that can only be walked alone
I walk forward so that
I won't fall behind other people's shadows
If I just head straight forward,
it'll appear right in front of me
Now, let's open the door
There are sparkling stars in this vast sky
If just I had wings,
I'd flap and flutter
high through the space like a bird
Going around the constellations,
and pursuing the stars
we had just started this endless journey
"Act 3: The Teddy Bear"