The dorm mother's box lunches
always look so good!
You think so? Looks average to me.
It's pretty brown.
I wish it had some cuter stuff in it.
Food always tastes great
when it's made just for you!
Right?
Yeah.
Hey, Narata isn't here.
Huh? Ai?
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone right now
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"The Teddy Bear"
What's up?
You know, if you eat alone out here,
the second-years will get on your case.
I don't want to eat lunch
in that tiny locker room.
And making small talk
with everyone's such a pain.
How are things going with
your roommate, Watanabe?
She seems fun.
Not in the least! She's not "fun" at all!
She's so loud, she doesn't listen,
and she can't read the room.
She's always rolling off the bed,
she never gets up on time.
I wish I could change rooms.
Wow.
You've changed a little, Ai.
You've never taken interest in other people.
I'm not interested in her!
She just keeps forcing
herself into my life.
She's so annoying.
I don't know. It seems like
you can't take your eyes off her.
You don't get it, Taichi.
You don't get how
unbearably annoying she is.
I don't think she's a bad person.
You should be friends.
I don't need friends.
If I want to talk, I'll talk to you.
I can never be friends with Watanabe.
Ai! Where were you?
Nowhere.
I thought you might be in the bathroom,
but you were gone so long.
Are you feeling okay?
Did you eat lunch?
Yep.
I'm worried about you not eating enough, Ai.
You needn't worry about me.
Don't say that! We're friends, aren't we?
We're not friends.
"Hana no Michi: Flower Way"
If I wait here, maybe I'll see Naracchi.
But we're roommates!
I want to be friends with you!
I don't really want to be
friends with anyone.
Huh?
Dealing with people is annoying
and a waste of my time.
No!
Hey, you girls! No shouting in the halls!
Sorry.
Let's go.
I don't need friends.
I just want to be as far away
as possible from the world of men.
That's all I want.
The words "you're so pretty!"
and "what a cutie!"
have always meant "hello" to me.
"Narata Family Memorial Event"
My goodness, Ai,
you just keep getting cuter!
I can't tell which one of you is the doll.
What a big teddy bear!
My daddy bought it for me!
Wow, really?
That's not true.
That's just what my mom said,
so it's probably not true.
So, who is your daddy, Ai?
I dunno.
That's the truth.
My mom is the famous
movie actress Narata Kimiko.
Ai's such a cutie.
No wonder she's popular.
My uncle Taichi is a ballet dancer.
That's not why.
They just want to know who her father is.
Well, so do I.
You know what the old man
in Hachioji said?
"You siblings keep chasing men's asses."
Hey, Narata!
Your mom was popping her titties on TV last night!
Your mom's titties are jiggly!
Stop it!
Boys are the worst!
Be little considerate to Ai!
It's okay, I don't care.
My mom's working really hard.
I've never been ashamed of her.
That's also a lie.
I've never even seen any of my mom's movies.
But my mom always tells me
that I'm the reason she works so hard.
And that cute girls
have to 'tough it out.'
It happened around the time I'd
gotten way bigger than Papa Bear.
This is Mr. Seiji.
He might be your new daddy someday!
It's real nice to meet you, Ai.
Hope we get along.
It's nice to meet you, too.
Mr. Seiji is such a nice guy, and he's
gonna live with us from here on out!
Huh?
My mom never told me where she met him,
or what he did for a living.
But that wasn't new.
She never told me anything.
Almost got it...
Yes!
I can see your undies.
You're such a cutie, Ai.
His smile made my stomach turn,
but it must've just been my imagination.
I mean, my mom picked him out.
He couldn't be bad.
He never even got mad at me.
So when he happened to be outside
the door when I got out of the bath,
or when his footsteps stopped
in front of my door,
it all had be a coincidence.
My mom's smart.
All grown-ups are.
They all know so much more than the children.
They'd never be wrong.
Ai!
I'm off to my one-week location shoot!
Be good for Mr. Seiji, okay?
Do your best at work.
And, uh, come home soon, okay?
What? C'mon, you're too old
for this baby nonsense.
Listen to Mr. Seiji now.
Okay, but...
You know I'm working myself
to death for you, right?
Yeah, that's it!
You're so good at this, Miki!
Ai, it's getting dark!
You should head home.
Okay.
Here, I made some cupcakes.
Take some home with you.
Wow! You made these?
You didn't buy them at a store?!
Bye-bye!
Ai doesn't go on playdates very often.
Really?
She's such a beauty, though.
Right?!
I don't wanna go home.
Huh?
Welcome back.
You're home late.
I was so worried about you.
I wasn't sure what you liked to eat,
so I ordered a whole bunch of things.
C'mon, let's have dinner.
No thanks.
I got a cupcake from my friend's house.
Really? That's too bad.
Y'know, I really want to be
friends with you, Ai.
B-But we are friends!
Really? Then to prove it,
will you give me a kiss?
Huh?
My cute little Ai.
You're such a good girl.
Wait, I don't--
Huh?
What is he doing?
Gross!
I'm dirty. I'm dirty.
He made me dirty!
His tongue moved around in my mouth
like a wet, warm slug.
You know what happens to dirty sluts?
They get pregnant!
He made me a dirty slut.
Oh, no. What if I get pregnant?
Maybe if I tie my tummy real tight,
it won't get big.
Mommy!
What's wrong?
I'm in the middle of a shoot.
Please come home quickly!
God, you've been such a baby lately!
I'm scared of him!
Of who? Mr. Seiji?
He's always staring at me!
And he waits for me
in front of my room! And he--
Here's the thing, Ai.
It's just girls being self-conscious is all.
I have to go.
But today he--
Come on, Ai. What am I going to do
with a little girl like you?
I actually knew everything all along.
My mom wasn't working hard for me.
She loved work more than she loved me.
My daddy didn't buy me this bear.
Because my mom's an actress,
and my dad's not around,
if I'm not perfect, everyone will
start gossiping about her.
That's why I pretended to be
a happy little girl.
I lied to everyone and stuffed
all those feelings down inside.
I won't be lonely! I'll be okay!
My daddy got it for me!
Mommy! Hey, Mommy!
I love you!
Now nobody can stuff
anything else inside me.
Ai, are you awake?
I'm coming in, okay?
What happened to your hair? Are you okay?
Do you want me to do anything?
Put a lock on my door, please.
A few days later, when my mom came back,
she had a huge fight with Taichi.
Here's the key to your room, Ai.
Thank you.
I have one more thing for you.
It's a lucky charm.
A key to my house.
If anything bad happens,
you can run away to my place anytime.
Years passed, and soon,
I was in junior high.
That man was still
leeching off of my family.
The lock on my door
kept any danger at bay,
and I learned that you can't
get pregnant from kissing.
Even still, I never felt safe.
The other kids started to call me
an emotionless "noh mask"
and it wasn't long before
I lost all my friends.
Pigs. I wish all men would die.
These thoughts rang out through my head as
I imagined mowing down men with gunfire.
Taichi can live, I guess.
"JPX48 Producer Kuroge Shun"
JPX48?
Yes, it's an idol group I'm producing.
It's a group of girls ages 14 and up.
An all-girl group.
When I saw your daughter, Ms. Narata,
I knew she'd be a perfect fit!
She's no good.
She's just not the type.
You see, that's what makes her perfect!
We need cool-headed girls like her, too.
Our studio's just down in Akihabara.
Akiba. That's where Taichi lives!
I'll do it.
What?!
I was so stupid.
I didn't even stop to think about the
target audience of an all-girl idol group.
Years later...
Let go, creep.
...it would lead to
my cold words that day.
Ugh, I can't believe her!
That Watanabe Sarasa! She must've
said something to you again!
She must've ticked you off.
It was my fault, anyway.
You're so sweet, Narata.
Just tell me if something unpleasant
happens with Watanabe again.
I'll handle it for you.
In tap dancing, you produce a rhythm
with the toe, ball, and heel of your foot.
You become a musical
instrument as you dance.
Feel the rhythm in your body.
Ball, heel, ball, heel, heel, heel.
Tap-tap, tap-tap, tap, tap.
Try it!
You catch on quick, Narata.
I shouldn't be surprised,
given your stage experience.
Watanabe!
You're too loud!
Huh?!
Your steps are too heavy!
Imagine they're being sucked down to the floor.
Light movements.
Mr. Narata told me the same thing!
He says I've got good control,
but I'm heavy!
Hey, you! Yamada!
You've gotten fatter.
U-Um, I have gained a little weight
since starting school...
A little? Try a lot!
But, you know?
Girls are cuter if they've got
a couple of curves! Right?
What? That's just what men want!
Listen, your biggest audience is women.
And women have a shrewd eye.
Kouka fans want a dreamlike fantasy!
A beauty they could never hope to obtain!
So no fatties. If you want to stay here,
you're going to have to shed those pounds!
I think it's a matter of self-control.
You're too easy on yourself, Yamada.
Stop it! She's already crying!
Be nice to her!
I'll never eat food again, I promise!
No! That's not good for your health!
Let's ask our dorm mom for advice
when we get back, okay?
Why is she like that?
Why does she keep shoving herself
into other people's business?
It makes her even more annoying.
Excuse me.
Do you remember me?
"Kouka School of
Musical and Theatrical Arts"
Watanabe,
have you seen Ai?
I think she already went back to the dorm.
All right.
Y'know, Watanabe, I really hope
you can be friends with Ai.
Sure, but she told me we weren't friends.
How am I supposed to be friends with her
after she said that to me?
What's wrong, Ai?
He's here. On the road.
Who's here?
The guy I called a creep at that fan event.
Oh, God! He followed me here!
What do I do?!
Hey!
I'll walk you back if you want.
Huh?
I mean, we're going back to the same room.
I might not be your friend,
but I can at least walk with you.
Sure, could you?
Huh?
Sure!
Let's go, Ai!
"NOTICE: Due to increased traffic,
loitering and/or asking Kouka students for
autographs in this area is prohibited."
I hear that singing a fun song can help
when you're feeling scared!
I'll sing something for you, then!
♬ Falling from the sky
like white snow... ♬
Let go, creep.
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing,
stalking a helpless girl like this?!
I, uh...
I just, uh, I...
...just wanted to talk
with Naracchi... er, Miss Narata.
First, here. You dropped
this earlier, Naracchi.
Here!
Go away.
Don't come closer!
Do you hate me 'cause I was mean to you?!
Are you here to get back at me?!
I just... I--!
Ai!
I'll keep walking on the path
that glows white in the darkness
A long, narrow path
that can only be walked alone
I walk forward so that
I won't fall behind other people's shadows
If I just head straight forward,
it'll appear right in front of me
Now, let's open the door
There are sparkling stars in this vast sky
If just I had wings,
I'd flap and flutter
high through the space like a bird
Going around the constellations,
and pursuing the stars
we had just started this endless journey
"Act 4: Tears Overwritten"