Go away.
Don't come closer!
Ai!
No, that's not it.
I just wanted
to apologize to her.
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone right now
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"Tears Overwritten"
What do I do?
I'm a horrible person.
I left Watanabe with him.
It's my fault Naracchi was forced to quit JPX.
What do you mean by that?
I'm not Ai, but if you want, I can hear you out.
I mean, I am her room-
Alright! No sharing personal information!
Mr. Narata?! What are you doing here?
I wasn't going to let the two of you go by yourselves.
Who knew if this guy was a total perv.
A... total perv?
He's not a perv, he's a stalker!
U-Um.
Perv, stalker, call me whatever you want.
It's my fault, anyway.
Sorry to bother you.
Please, wait!
Ai might've told me that we weren't friends,
but even though it sucks,
I still want to try to be friends with her!
Could you please tell me what happened
between you two, Mister Stalker?
Watanabe Sarasa's with a guy? No way!
He's super lame, though.
It suits her in a way.
Here.
Thanks.
What, Mr. Narata's there, too?
Thank you!
Um,
I used to be an unemployed shut-in
who never left the house.
Wow, Mister Shut-In!
I was never good with people,
so I started ditching school.
I spent every day watching anime,
playing games, and browsing the internet.
I love anime, too!
I'm super into Floor Kings right no-
C'mon, let him talk.
Sorry!
One day,
I somehow had this music show on.
What? Who is this girl?!
And why does she never try to smile?
It shocked me.
She was not scared, or withered.
She reminded me of a fantasy princess,
or an ice queen who rules over the winter itself.
But then, there was that unforgettable day.
"Local Mascot Meet n' Greet"
Today, we've brought a bunch of your
favorite local mascots to meet the JPX48!
Which is your favorite, Komomo?
Oh, wow, I think I like Starry Boy the best!
I knew 100% she'd fallen from heaven!
That day, June 23rd, the Naracchi Nation
opened to one and all!
"ANONYMOUS: WELCOME TO
THE NARACCHI NATION"
"ANONYMOUS: She's kinda cute"
Like when Commodore Perry came to Japan!
Even I want to...
I want to...
I want to open my borders, too!
I don't need to worry about how others see me.
I can just be myself.
A fellow Naracchi stan?
I made friends and started a part-time job.
"JPX48 Handshake Event"
Please double-checking the number
on your ticket before lining up!
"Ai Narata"
How shall I express myself in such a limited time?
Will I be able to convey my millions of feelings?
I have to thank you. I have to!
I have to tell you!
I-I...
Naracchi, I...
I love you so much!
Hey, sir-
Let go, creep.
It took so long to crawl my way up,
but only a second to fall back into the abyss.
That's when I remembered.
"Yeah, I'm just a gross nerd."
It's not your fault at all, Mister Gross Nerd!
You poor guy! Cheer up, Mister Gross Otaku!
N-No, you don't need to worry about me.
But to make up for it,
"RIP Naracchi lmao"
"does she hate her fans??" "GJ Naracchi."
Naracchi was forced to graduate without any ceremony.
It was my fault for holding onto
Naracchi's hand for too long.
"Ai Narata EXPELLED from JPX"
But I was just one guy.
There wasn't anything I could do about it.
I knew it might've been selfish of me,
but I wanted to at least apologize to her.
But that probably just makes me
even more of a creep to Naracchi, huh?
You don't seem like a bad person.
What's your name?
Mister Creepy Nerd.
Okay, Creepy Nerd.
Uh, sure, just call me that.
So I've got good news and bad news.
The good news is that Ai
doesn't hate you specifically.
She hates every man in the world.
Huh?
She'd been holding back for the whole handshaking event.
And she just happened to break when it was your turn.
Now for the bad news:
Ai isn't as attached to JPX as you hope.
Unfortunately, I can probably say the
same thing about the Kouka Troupe.
"Tear Spray"
At some point, Ai gave up on the world
and started hiding her emotions.
Right now, she's just trying to find a
place where she can relax and feel safe.
Dealing with people is annoying
and a waste of my time.
It's such a waste.
I mean, the first time I saw Ai,
I thought she looked like Alice stumbling into Wonderland.
"How perfect for Kouka," I thought.
"She would be the type of person to stand
and shine in the center of the Kouka stage."
I knew I wanted to stand up on that stage with her.
Narata, where are you going?
It's almost time for dinner.
Watanabe's not back yet.
I'm going to go look for her.
I saw her alone with a guy earlier.
Huh?
Excuse me!
What a great pic.
Now, what should I do with it?
She's not here. What do I do?.
What if he did something to her?
What?
You're not half bad.
I am a rising Kouka star, after all!
Well then, can you do this?
Matrix!
Like this?
Ai!
You came back. What's up?
What the hell?
Huh?
I really
hate you!
You... hate me?
Well, this is unusual.
I can barely hear you, Watanabe.
Usually you're far too loud than necessary.
Sorry, sir.
And Yamada, you too.
S-Sorry!
I'm on a diet right now, so I don't have the energy.
Oh? Well, diet's fine, but take care of yourself, okay?
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's split into quartets!
Yamada, Hoshino, Narata, and Watanabe!
Hey, Ai?
I don't know why you got so mad at me.
Could you tell me why?
Uh... Ai?
If I tell you, will you finally leave me alone?
Huh?
I felt horrible for running off
and leaving you there with him.
It took me everything to go back.
And yet, it was so foolish.
What was foolish?
You guys were dancing and
seemed like having fun, that was foolish!
Ai...
That doesn't make sense.
Huh?
If you came back because you were worried
about me, then you should've been happy!
If you were worried, you should've
been glad to see I was okay.
You're just trying to pick a fight now!
Just don't bother me anymore!
Fine, then! We're through!
Nothing's through!
I told you, we aren't friends!
I told a someone I wanted to be
friends with that "we're through."
"We're through"?
But I still can't bring myself to hate her.
She has so many qualities that I don't.
I can't help but admire her.
You don't need to rush since
you're just getting to know each other.
Just take your time and keep at it.
But you might not get what you want.
Your feelings could just be one-sided forever,
which you can only watch over.
But I think that's beautiful in its own way.
One-sided feelings forever, huh?
Akiya is so poetic sometimes.
Dammit, Kouzaburou!
Stop tweeting and pretending to be me!
I figured it would be too heavy
for you to handle, Akiya.
Let her be late.
I don't want to go to class.
Watanabe!
Yes, Mr. Narata.
I can't find Ai. Have you seen her?
Oh, I thought she felt bad and went back to the dorm.
Is she skipping class?
I hope that's it.
It doesn't look like she went back to the dorm,
and she's not picking up her phone.
Ai's not the type to wander around town,
because of how she sticks out.
And she wouldn't want to give strangers
any reason to talk to her,
so she's likely not breaking any rules.
Thanks. I'll keep looking for her.
Um, do you think she might've been feeling
homesick and went back to Tokyo?
I really doubt that's the case.
Watanabe?
Could we borrow you for a moment?
I wish Watanabe would drop out of school.
Whoa, hol' up, isn't that Naracchi from JPX?
Huh?
Yo, it totally is!
Holy shit, cute as hell!
Where could Ai have gone?
Did she run away because I said we were through?
No way, she wouldn't.
Watanabe!
Y-Yeah!
Are you listening?
This is you, right?
"That's a Kouka student, right?"
Whoa, that's me! It's totally me!
"I thought their school rules
were stricter than this?"
And they've blacked out my eyes!
So you admit it, then?
That he's your boyfriend?
Huh?
The Kouka Troupe does allow romantic relationships,
but you can't be so open about it that
others can get a picture of you two alone.
Especially when you're still a student.
Oh, but we weren't alone.
Mr. Narata was with us.
Really? I'll confirm it with him, then.
Oh, no. If this gets out, I'm sure a few
second-years will have it out for you.
But I guess your boyfriend is worth it.
He's not my boyfriend, though.
Um, can we continue this later?
Where are you going?
I just remembered something important I gotta do!
Don't you dare go!
It was you, wasn't it?
Huh?
You took it way too far this time.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Do you hate me or something, Risa?
"Call from Sarasa Watanabe"
Hello?
Actually, I'm still in Kobe.
Naracchi?
I'm bored of the ocean.
I've never skipped school before,
so I don't know what to do next.
I wonder if they noticed I'm gone,
or if they're even worried about me.
Hey, 'scuse me!
I'm kinda lost. Could you help?
Whoa, hol' up, are you Naracchi?
Yay, how 'bout a selfie?
Stop.
Stop it!
Let go, you creeps!
Yo, what the hell?
Why is it so hard for me to live in this world?
He just wanted a selfie!
Why do I have to be like this?
No. Please.
Please stop.
Hey!
Stop that, right now!
Get your dirty paws
off of her!
What the heck?
She obviously doesn't like it!
I'm telling you to let her go!
What?
I'm not scared!
I'm not scared of someone like you!
Oh, no... what do I do?
Whoa, she really was here!
Ai!
I said we were through, Ai,
but I'll help you just this once.
Just this once, okay?
Help! These guys won't leave us alone!
She's so loud.
Help!
And she's huge.
These guys are harassing two sweet, innocent girls!
Shit, cops!
Fine, we'll let you off the hook this time!
Weaklings.
You shouldn't do that!
You're coming to the station with us!
Wait, that's the wrong guy!
You're a teacher at Kouka?
Yes. My name is Narata Taichi.
How did you know I was here?
Mister Creepy Nerd figured it out!
I got his number before he left.
The ocean! She's gotta be near the ocean!
Why?
March 2018 issue of POCO mag
and the JPX official newsletter,
she said the ocean makes her feel calm!
That doesn't really
narrow it down, though.
I'll do a search on social media!
This is bad. I gotta find her...
I gotta find her, fast!
And then he really did find you!
Isn't that awesome?!
Mister Creepy Nerd really
cares about you, Ai.
Watanabe, could you tell them your side of the story?
Sure!
Huh?
You've got blood. Wipe it with this.
I didn't mean to.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This is the best I can do right now.
It's okay.
Really, it's okay. Please don't cry.
I-- no, we only ever wanted
to see you smile, Naracchi.
I don't think I'll ever get this close to you again,
so please let me keep your handkerchief.
I'm sorry for scaring you before.
One day, I'll come see you perform
on the big Kouka stage.
When that day comes,
I hope I'll see your beautiful smile once more.
Farewell.
And thank you. Until we meet again!
"Hana no Michi: Flower Way"
Mister Creepy Nerd was a pretty nice guy.
Oh, and his real name is Kitaouji Mikiya!
It sounds so cool.
Hey, if there's something I want to forget, but can't,
what should I do about it?
Not surprised. Anybody would be weirded
out by a random question like that.
Well, I'm only 15, so there's a lot
I have to learn about the world.
If you can't forget something that happened,
you can make new memories by having fun and doing the things you love.
Just keep overwriting the bad memories
with lots of good ones,
and eventually, the bad ones will fade away.
Because I was walking behind her,
I couldn't see the expression
on her face when she said that.
When we got back, the second-years were waiting for us.
For the following week,
Watanabe and I had our cleaning hours doubled.
Try opening that tightly and strongly clenched fist
Pieces of dreams will fall off from the palm
Gently put the important ones on the fingertips
Butterflies' wings are spreading
Petals are scattering
Gracefully than anything
If you just wanna move forward, forget lovers and friends
Dreams that lose their radiance become nothing but a stone
Let's fly higher than anyone
while tenderly embracing our dreams
"Act 5: The Chosen Maidens"