Whoa, have you lost weight, Yamada-san?
Huh?
You totally have!
Your tummy's way flatter!
My diet must be working!
H-Hey, Watanabe-san?
Sugimoto-san, what's that
pose you're doing?
I-It's the Winter Troupe's special pose!
How do you not know that, Watanabe-san?!
Every Kouka fan knows that!
Watanabe-san, I've been meaning
to ask this for quite a while,
but do you like any other shows
besides The Rose of Versailles?
Umm, well, I don't know
many other shows...
Look! You've traumatized
our poor class rep!
Sugimoto-san loves
the Winter Troupe most of all!
Uh, Sugimoto-san?
This is fine.
No, this is wonderful!
Oh, Watanabe-san, we're going to see a
Winter Troupe performance this afternoon.
They're doing Romeo and Juliet.
This is the perfect chance for you to
fall in love with a show that isn't RoV!
We get to see a show?!
Yes, a few shows every year!
Seeing shows is an important part
of our Kouka education!
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone right now
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"The Chosen Maidens"
It's just like the theater I went to
in Tokyo when I was little!
Shh! Quiet down, Watanabe-san!
Oh, right!
Um, Watanabe-san, I--
Hey, you're from JPX!
C'mon, don't point it out, Sei!
Oh, sorry.
Good afternoon, ma'am!
You in the hundredth class?
You girls are so cute.
How's the Phantom doing?
Andou-sensei is doing well, thank you!
He's an ex-actor,
so he's always had trouble
fitting in with the other teachers.
Help make his life easier, okay?
Of course!
Who was that lovely lady?!
You don't know?! She's the number two star
in the Winter Troupe, Sei Satomi!
Sei-sama isn't in today's show.
I wish we could've seen her Tybalt.
Tybalt is double-cast in this show.
Wait, this show is the final performance
of the Winter Troupe's
top star, Sou Kazahana.
But if Sei-sama isn't going to be
taking over for the rest of the shows,
then that means...
Sei Satomi-sama might be
the next top star of the Winter Troupe!
Your nose is bleeding!
So that means I was just talking to
the next top star of the troupe?
That's right! We're so lucky today!
Hey, Taichi, what am I supposed to do?
I said something horrible to Watanabe-san.
I want to apologize, but I've never
fought with a friend before.
I don't know how to make up with someone!
You speak of peace between
the Capulets and Montagues? What folly!
There is naught 'twixt
our families but hate, villain!
Romeo!
O, Juliet! Let us be one in death!
Let hate return to hate,
and love return to love!
My love is forever yours, Romeo!
This is Kouka...
That was so wonderful!
We'll get to stand on that stage
in two years' time.
I know! I'm so excited!
O, how my heart races!
I would fly o'er these walls
with these wings of love for you!
Those are Romeo's lines.
Watanabe-san hasn't seen
any other show besides RoV, right?
So she memorized them
after hearing them just once?
With what words should I profess
my deepest love for you?
O, Juliet!
Look! Upon the pitch-black
curtain of night...
...sparkle a thousand brilliant stars!
Everyone must have noticed it
in that moment.
Without thinking, they looked up to
the sky and saw themselves there.
But did they see what I saw?
That amongst the sea of glimmering stars,
there was one bright star,
shining above all others?
Twinkling high in the sky,
brighter than any in its midst...
That star was Sarasa Watanabe.
That was where she belonged.
Where I belonged.
I want to see the world from up there.
Don't think too hard about
what you want her to think about you.
Work up your courage
to express your feelings
and speak them, honest and true,
with words of love.
Um, I...
I want to be friends
with you, Watanabe-san!
I'm so glad!
I thought my feelings
would be one-sided forever.
Ever since the first moment
I met you, Ai-chan,
I knew I wanted to be friends with you!
Right.
Thanks.
H-Hey, why are you crying, Yamada?
I'm just so relieved!
I can't help it!
You guys all okay?
July arrived.
We changed into our summer uniforms
and grew closer to one another.
More and more often we called each other
by first names or nicknames.
My personal goal:
call Sarasa Watanabe "Sarasa."
Unfortunately, it was
a tough challenge for me.
Watanabe-san.
What's up, Ai-chan?
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay! Don't fall in!
That's weird. I thought girls always
went to the bathroom together.
Oh, right, Ai-chan!
You wanna come with?!
No.
Our midterm results
just got posted in the hall!
Wanna go check them out together?
Yeah.
"Midterm Test Results"
"#1: Sawa Sugimoto"
Sawa's top of the class, as usual.
She did well enough before
to be our class rep, after all.
"#11: Kaoru Hoshino"
24th in the class. Not good, not bad.
Yay! I moved up a bit!
I went from 40th to 39th!
Sa...
Nice, Watanabe-san.
I know! I'm so happy, Ai-chan!
"#39: Sarasa Watanabe"
"#40: Ayako Yamada"
Oh, no...
I have the worst grades in the class now.
♬ Lead along by
the lovely spring breeze... ♬
Oh, come on! Yamada-san,
I can't hear you at all!
I'm sorry.
Are you feeling okay, honey?
Getting enough sleep, eating well?
Yeah, I'm eating enough.
First they told me not to eat,
now they want me to eat?
Can they make up their minds?
"Take Me to Them"
How did I even get in here, anyway?
I was eight when I saw my first
Kouka Troupe performance,
and I was completely captivated
by the fantastic world I saw.
Every year after that, I would always see
a Kouka show on my birthday,
and I would only sing
Kouka songs at karaoke.
In middle school, I started taking ballet.
My family runs a bakery.
We didn't have lots of money,
but when my parents saw
their quiet, shy daughter
passionately pursuing something,
they pushed themselves
the extra mile for me.
I-I did it!
My adult sister thought...
What?! You wanna go into Kouka?!
Yeah. They have a music school in Kobe.
I thought about applying.
But you're only in tenth grade.
You can already apply?
Oh, yeah.
Whoa, last year's admittance rate was
worse than Tokyo U? What the hell?!
Yeah, so I probably won't get in.
I just thought it'd be nice.
Why not try to get in, then?
Yeah, I know... wait, what?
You've always loved singing, Ayako.
There was never anything I wanted to do,
so I just snagged an office job.
But if you've got a dream,
you should go after it, y'know?
And if you're wrong and totally get in,
I'll help pay for your tuition!
When I got accepted, my mom and dad
were so happy for me.
My sister, on the other hand, sobbed.
You did it, Ayako!
You're freakin' amazing!
I'm so happy for you!
I have no right to say
I want to quit after all that.
Or that I can't keep up with my classes.
I wanna play Sukeroku and stamp my feet
and walk out on the hanamichi!
Sounds great. I can't wait to see it.
Sara--
Watanabe-san, is everything okay?
Huh?
Oh, I'm okay! I just don't like
the sound of cicadas is all.
And 'cause I'm tall,
I'm closer to the sun,
which means I get hit with more UV rays.
Is that a thing?
Hey, guys, our family in Hokkaido
sent us some monaka!
Tokachi's known for their
super-good red beans!
"Hokkaido Red Bean Monaka"
I heard that in the past, if your
final first-year grades were bad,
they made you drop out.
Guess that's how they
weeded out poor candidates.
That's so mean!
Oh hey, Ai-chan, what was your rank?
24th. I'm gonna do better, though.
I finally know what I want to do,
so I'm gonna give it my all.
Might as well aim for the top.
Right, you just "haven't been
actually trying this whole time."
One day, I'm gonna be one of
the Kouka Troupe's top stars.
Ai-chan!
I shouldn't. I shouldn't
compare myself to her.
Naracchi's on a whole
different level than I am.
I can't seem to throw up anymore.
And fatties can't stay in Kouka.
Oh, sis...
Hit that falsetto! Keep that
throat open and hold it!
Hold it! Keep going!
Yamada-san, what's the matter?
Are you sure you're feeling okay?
Sorry, sir. I'm fine.
Yeah, sure, you're sorry.
Hey, Yamada!
Did you lose weight?
Yes, I lost around five kilograms.
Good. Don't hurt yourself, though.
I want you to give me a daily report on
everything you've eaten, starting today.
Yes, ma'am.
Do I have to lose even more weight?
"Ayako Yamada Food Log"
Why the long face, Tachibana-sensei?
It's Ayako Yamada.
She's binging and purging.
That explains why she lost weight,
and why her fingers were so red.
Tachibana-sensei, did you really
tell Yamada-san she was a "fatty"?
I sure did.
I can't believe you! Why were you
so cruel to her?!
You need to watch
what you say to these girls!
Onodera-sensei, while being
nice to them is all fine and dandy,
when they join the troupe,
they're going to be subjected
to all sorts of verbal abuse.
And the more popular they become,
the more abuse they'll get.
S-Sure, but--
Weak women can't survive in show business.
Or are you telling Yamada to be so
unremarkable that no one will hate on her?
Th-That's not what I'm--
She needs to grow a backbone now.
Sure, but Yamada-san
is especially sensitive.
Then if she quits, it's just proof
she'd never make it.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
In either case, we need to
get her to stop throwing up.
I bet your back hurts right here.
Narata-san, what are you doing here?
I had to pee.
Your back doesn't hurt from working out.
A girl in JPX was doing the same thing.
Your stomach acid agitates
your esophagus. That's why it hurts.
Your esophagus goes right up
the middle of your back.
Yeah, so?!
Losing weight that way
won't make you prettier.
I don't wanna hear that,
not from someone who's always been pretty!
I'm sorry.
I want my big sister...
"Class A Music Materials"
Today, we're going to use all our class
time to hear a solo from everyone!
It's fun to mix things up, right?
Pick a song you like out of these three.
Why don't you start us off, Yamada-san?
"Take Me to Them"
Which song are you singing?
Yamada-san? Are you okay?
Whoa, Aya!
--Aya-chan!
--Yamada-san!
"Medical Center"
Looks like regular pharyngitis.
Your immune system's responding,
and you've got a fever.
You should take it easy for a few days
and get plenty of rest.
Um, I'm...
It's hard to talk, too, huh?
You should rest your voice, too.
I'm a Kouka student.
Wow! You're going to be
a big star someday, huh?
But my grades suck,
and I'm this close to failing out.
I don't want to miss class.
I'll get left behind.
Could you just give me
something for my fever?
I'm afraid I can't recommend that.
We don't want to make your throat
swell up. You won't be able to breathe.
You just need to take things easy.
You rest up, okay?
Just focus on getting better. Got it, hon?
My back hurts.
"You workin' hard, Ayako?"
"One of the girls at my shop is a huge
Kouka fan! She's so excited for you.
Color me a proud big sister"
"Hey, sis"
"What? You on break right now?"
"I wanna eat those cookies you bake"
"OK! I'll make them next time you're home"
"I wanna eat mom's oyakodon"
"I'll tell her!!"
"I wanna eat dad's cream-filled buns"
Ayako. I don't have any special skills,
so I can't say I understand your world
but if you're suffering, or in pain,
you can always come home!
"Ayako. I don't have any special skills,
so I can't say I understand your world
but if you're suffering, or in pain,
you can always come home!!!"
Sis...
I should go back to
the world I knew before.
I know I was just chasing after dreams
that would never come true.
But it was nice to get a little closer
to a world where they did.
Yamada-san! You're in there, right?
I have to tell you something!
Onodera-sensei, what are you doing?
You know only students
are allowed to be here!
This is an emergency!
Pretend I'm not here!
Men are strictly forbidden from--
Well, I'm a beautiful Kouka girl
on the inside!
Listen, Yamada-san.
You're a sweet and sensitive girl.
You must keep all your worries
to yourself, right?
But you're still so young!
You have so much time
to decide what you want from life!
It's totally normal to lose faith
or stumble here and there!
You might be the bottom of the class,
but you're miles ahead of the other
1,095 girls who didn't get in!
The Kouka Troupe only opens
to its chosen maidens!
And they only open for them just once!
Once you walk out, you can never go back!
I don't want you to quit, not yet!
I know you're forgetting
something important.
Girls with nothing to offer
don't get into Kouka!
Please, remember for me. What is it
you have? What's your special talent?
My voice?
That's right, your voice!
You know what I thought
when I heard your voice?
I thought, this girl's going to be
the next great etoile of our time!
Imagine you, on stage during
the grand finale of a Kouka show,
standing in the center of those big stairs
and singing acapella
with your beautiful voice!
Okay, girls! Today, we're going to
work on our sight--
Sorry I'm late!
Oh, Yamada-san!
Are you okay to sing again?
Yes, sir. My doctor gave me permission
to come to class again, too!
Well then, why don't we pick up from
where we left off the other day?
Solo time! Let's start with you,
Yamada-san, since you're feeling better!
Huh? Oh...
Aya-chan! You can use my sheet music!
Thanks, Sarasa-chan!
This is the song I sang
during my audition.
Okay, Yamada-san, step forward.
If I don't give up, will it be
just as Onodera-sensei says?
Will I stand in the center of
those big stairs one day,
getting a huge round of
applause just for myself?
Nobody can say for sure...
I didn't know Aya-chan
could sing like this!
I had no idea!
She sings like an angel!
I knew. I was in the same group
as her during auditions.
The moment she started singing,
the teachers snapped out of
their dazes to listen.
It always annoyed me how
she was never really trying in class.
The one thing I can say...
...is that if I quit now,
that's really the end.
Hey, I have to apologize.
You were worried about me, Narata-san,
and I just snapped at you.
I'm really sorry!
It's fine.
Huh?
I haven't spent much time
with other people before,
so I was probably too blunt.
Everyone says I act like a robot, or that
they don't know what I'm thinking.
That's not true!
You're different, Sara-- Watanabe-san.
But I can't stay like this.
I want to be an actress.
It's kind of a relief to know that even
you have stuff you worry about, Naracchi.
Oh, s-sorry.
It's okay.
Your soprano is so beautiful, Aya-chan!
I would love to sing like that, but since
Lady Oscar is an otokoyaku-role,
I won't get to sing soprano.
Have you always wanted to
play Lady Oscar, Sarasa-chan?
Yeah, ever since I was a kid!
Oh, though I guess there was a time
when I wanted to play Sukeroku.
"Act 6: A Glimpse of Stardom"