Since we got here it's just been
"basics, basics, basics"!
That's all we've done, every single class
since we started here!
And the Phantom's class is the worst!
We could ask for something different.
Let's ask Andou-sensei!
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone yet
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"A Glimpse of Stardom"
Today, we'll be talking about the
Stanislavski technique and how to--
Why do you all look dead?
Andou-sensei! Can I make a suggestion?
She's doing it.
She's actually asking.
What are you girls plotting?
Shoot, Watanabe.
Thanks!
So, there's one crucial skill that
every other teacher has mentioned to us.
Expression!
Expression.
I knew who every teacher was
without her even saying their names.
And?
And I believe the one class
where we'll learn
how to express ourselves is this one.
We've been Kouka students for four months,
so we think it might be nice if we, well,
had a little opportunity to actually act.
Is that your suggestion?
Well, I've been here eight years, and the
first-year's curriculum has never changed.
First-year students are expected to sit
politely and learn the basics of acting.
That's how it's been done at
the Kouka School for a century now.
But here's an idea, Watanabe!
Do that again.
Huh?
Show me what I sound like
when I say "expression."
If I think it's good,
I'll consider your suggestion.
Those are high stakes!
Got a lot of pressure on me,
but here goes...
Expression? What's that,
some hot new band?
Okay, open your textbooks.
That's it.
So much for that.
Sorry I couldn't help.
Actually, Sara--
Watanabe-san, that was a good
impression of Andou-sensei.
It so was!
Maybe it was too good.
Oh, Watanabe-san!
There's a package here for you.
13, 14, 15, 16 roses.
Sara-- Watanabe-san, is today...
Yep! I turn 16 years old today!
Huh?!
Today's your birthday?!
Why didn't you tell us?!
Happy birthday!
Aww, thanks!
My first friend's birthday is today...
So who gave you this bouquet of roses?
Is it a guy?!
Ohmigosh, your boyfriend?!
Maybe! He lives in Tokyo,
so we're long-distance right now,
but it could be him!
A-And he's a real, live person?
Not some anime guy?
Is that the person
you're always messaging?
"Happy Birthday"
"from your fan of the red rose"
What the hell? That's kind of creepy.
Sara-- Watanabe-san, does your boyfriend
like these sorts of gestures?
That's hard to say.
"Kouzaburou"
You sure are in a good mood.
Why wouldn't I be?
It's my darling Sarasa's 16th birthday.
You knew that, right, Akiya?
Of course I did!
So, did you send her a present?
You are her boyfriend, right?
I'm gonna give it to her
when she comes home this summer.
C'mon, where's your passion?
I sent her a bouquet of 16 roses.
She's so incredibly special to me.
And this is her special day.
Wait... hold on.
Don't worry, I didn't say it was from me.
I said it was from
her "fan of the red rose."
"Happy Birthday"
"from your fan of the red rose"
I said it was from
her "fan of the red rose."
"Happy Birthday"
"from your fan of the red rose"
Her fan of the red rose?
Forget summer vacation. Why not just
send her something now?
I'll send her a text message tonight.
You gonna stop by her grandpa's
place tonight again?
Yeah, that's the plan.
"Happy Birthday, Sarasa-chan! I'll give you
your present over summer break!"
Her boyfriend's a frog? And a bot at that.
But why does a bot have a private account?
I won't let that frog outdo me.
I wanna give Watanabe-san something
she'll love even more than those roses.
After all, she's the first
friend I ever made.
And now's the perfect chance
to call her by her first name.
Should I add -chan because
she's younger than me?
Sarasa-tan? Saracchi?
Or do I keep it simple with Sarasa?
Oh, geez!
Oh my God!
The hardest-to-get lottery prize figurine
of Tsukahara Vault Taku!
Oh, Taku-sama!
Ai-chan, you got this for me,
didn't you?! I could cry!
I tried four times to win it
and only won hand towels!
Well, Sara--
Watanabe-san, you're always
going on and on about Floor Kings,
so I gave it a go and won the top prize.
In one try?!
No, after a half-dozen tries.
You like it?
I love it!
Especially this part!
"To Sarasa. Sorry it's late.
Happy birthday."
Don't read it out loud!
But look!
"To Sarasa"!
Look, Sa... Watanabe-san.
Just call me Sarasa!
We're friends, aren't we, Ai-chan?
Sarasa.
Oh, Taku-sama! Ai-chan called me "Sarasa"!
I can die happy now!
Oh, right.
I had a meeting with
the other teachers yesterday,
and they said we could
change up the curriculum.
Quiet down.
We're going to perform a scene from
Shakespeare's Romeo and Juliet.
The roles are Romeo, Juliet,
Tybalt, and Juliet's Nurse.
Each group of four will have two weeks
to prepare their scene on their own.
There you go.
On our own?
Andou-sensei, what do you mean
by "on our own"?
Is this not a class activity?
We got duped.
Some teacher he is.
Now, now, I did have to fight a bit
in that faculty meeting.
They let us do this under the assumption
that this would be an experiment.
So I haven't prepared any materials
or plans for guiding you to perform.
You'll rehearse on your own,
then in two weeks,
we'll spend one class period
presenting our scenes,
and I'll give you thorough
feedback on your performances.
Also, since this was your idea,
you won't complain if we end up
using it for next year's class, right?
Crafty bastard.
Of course, we don't have to do it.
We'll do it!
We drew lots to determine
who'd be in each of the five groups.
Group E.
"Group E"
"Sarasa Watanabe"
"Hoshino Kaoru"
"Chika Sawada"
Guess we're with you, Sarasa.
Yep! Let's break a leg, Group E!
How do we wanna pick roles?
Sarasa and I both want to be otoko-yaku,
so we'll pick between Romeo and Tybalt.
Rock-paper-scissors?
Sure!
Then Naracchi and I will play
the musume-yaku parts!
Want to do rock-paper-scissors, too?
Sure.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Sweet! I'll take Romeo!
That means I'm Tybalt!
What about you two?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Um, I'll play, uh, Ju...
Juliet's Nurse!
Huh?
I mean, I wanted to play that! A comic
role will be the perfect challenge!
You'll make a better Juliet
than me, anyway, Naracchi.
Really? I can play Juliet?!
Of course!
--I've always loved the Kouka version
of Juliet! I'm so happy right now!
--Oh, it's fine.
--I've always loved the Kouka version
of Juliet! I'm so happy right now!
I wanted to play the Nurse, anyway!
Okay. Then Naracchi's our Juliet.
Yep.
"Tatami Room"
Let's start with a quick readthrough.
To be honest, I think Sarasa
would be better off as Romeo
instead of the darker Tybalt.
Especially after that evening when
we were walking back from the theater,
and she recited those few
perfect lines as Romeo...
Okay, you start, Chika.
Got it!
Madam, your mother craves a word with you.
Good woman! Who is her mother?
Why sir, her mother is the lady
of the house, Lady Capulet.
A Capulet?! O dear account!
She's up next.
Show me the passion that's
driving you to become a top star.
Show us all you've got!
That voice, is that Romeo?
Romeo, of house Montague?
How dare the man come hither,
to the Cap... Capulet? Mansion itself...
How are you this bad?!
S-Sorry!
Stop messing around and get serious!
I-I wasn't messing around.
Whatever! We don't have time for this.
Juliet, your lines are next!
See?! Your crappy reading
threw Naracchi off!
My, what are you all doing here?
Good morning, Senpai!
What's this about? Some secret meeting?
Just kidding! Andou-sensei filled us
all in on your little scene exercise.
You first-years are already getting
to act? Boy, you girls are lucky!
And you're doing Romeo and Juliet?
I love that show!
One thing, though: you really can't
use this room to practice, mmkay?
"First-Year Lockers"
Hijiri-senpai was really mad at us.
She was? But she was all smiles.
That's how you can tell when
she's angry--she's smiling!
Ugh, we can't use the tatami room anymore.
Where should we practice
from now on, then, Kaoru?
Group A's using the lecture hall,
but they might let us share it.
Hey, can we use half
the lecture hall with you?
I don't see why not.
--Sure.
--Yeah.
W-We can't!
Why not?
W-We're doing the same scene,
so we'll throw each other off!
I don't wanna share a place
to practice with another group!
Then where do we practice?
All the other rooms are already taken.
Why don't we just do it
out on the sidewalk?
What?
The sidewalk?! Are you insane?!
We are students of the 100th class
of the esteemed Kouka School!
We can't perform on the sidewalk!
What a way to ruin Kouka for everyone!
We might be students now, but we are
destined to be professionals!
You'd better drill that
into your skull, got it?!
I have to use the bathroom.
That scared me.
Who pissed her off? You know
she's got a really short fuse.
I wouldn't say that.
Her mom was a Kouka actress,
and her grandma was a top musume-yaku.
I can't imagine the kind of pressure
that puts on her.
Hoshino-san.
Yeah, I know. I'm a loudmouth
with a short fuse, sorry.
There was a girl like you in JPX.
She was our group leader
and was always angry.
What, you come to rub it in?
I never went to high school, and barely
went to elementary and middle school.
So Sarasa wasn't the reason I couldn't
read Juliet's lines this morning.
I...
...can't read kanji.
"Favorite Place: beech"
"Why: Its suthing"
Back in JPX, I was used to my manager
writing the readings down for me.
This morning was the first time
I realized how screwed I am.
None of us have any experience,
so unless you get mad at us,
we'll just end up holding you back.
What the hell? That's so not fair.
What if I don't want to be
the bad guy, huh?
Then Group E fails together.
Is that a threat?!
"Nono Park"
Ta-dah! Well? Isn't it perfect?
It's not the sidewalk, that's for sure!
Chika-chan and I looked all over
for a good spot to practice!
Will this work, Kaoru?
Not like we can go anywhere else.
Okay, we've got two weeks to prep this
scene that's not gonna teach us anything.
C'mon, Group E!
Let's do this!
Really, Sugimoto-san?
You're gonna lend me your Blu-ray of
Winter Troupe Romeo and Juliet?
Kaoru asked me to.
She said if you don't level up, and fast,
then "Group E's gonna drag
the rest of our class down with them."
That Hoshino-san doesn't mince words, huh!
Ai-chan!
Sugimoto-san lent me her copy
of Romeo and Juliet! Wanna watch?
"Kanji Dictionary"
I'm good. I gotta spend all night
writing kanji readings onto our script.
Okay! Could I borrow your
Blu-ray player and headphones?
Sure.
I'm gonna study so hard, I'm gonna
knock the socks off Hoshino-san!
Mmkay.
Let's do an awesome job tomorrow morning!
Yep.
I wonder where the Sarasa
I saw that day disappeared to.
That voice, is that Romeo?
Romeo, of house Montague?
How dare the man come hither,
to the Capulet mansion itself!
Such sins shall not be endured!
Such sins shall not be endured.
So, how's your Group E looking, Kaoru?
And by that, I mean, how's Sarasa?
I kinda don't know.
Like, it's kind of creepy.
Creepy how?
You know how you're supposed to
improve little by little?
Sarasa just...
I'm so nervous.
It's okay. Andou-sensei doesn't
expect us to be good.
Then why did the Phantom
even want us to do this?
Probably because he wanted
to see how much fun we'd have,
or how much effort we'd put into it?
Seriously?
I mean, isn't playing pretend
way more fun when you've got friends?
We only had two weeks
to put this together,
but I'm sure that even when I
finally get to play Lady Oscar,
I'll remember these last two weeks.
Enough about Oscar. That was fun, though.
It doesn't matter if we mess up.
Just keep going until the end.
But give it your all, okay?!
Yeah! We'll give it 100% to the very end!
Okay, each group gets
15 minutes to perform.
I've marked out the 'stage' with tape,
so use that as a guide.
Group A is first...
...most of the time,
so let's go with Group E.
We have to go first?!
We didn't even think about
the size of the actual stage.
Okay, let's imagine it now!
There's a balcony up above,
and a big ballroom in the center.
The lights are tinged with blue,
and there's a crescent moon
through the window.
What beauty!
She shines like
a rich jewel amidst the crowd!
Love! This, truly, is love!
--My life's road has led me
to her beautiful flame!
--C'mon, now.
--My life's road has led me
to her beautiful flame!
Stop trying to gauge my reaction.
Keep looking at me,
and you'll flub your lines.
Good woman! Who is her mother?
--Why sir, her mother is the
lady of the house, Lady Capulet.
--She sure is spry for an old lady.
--Why sir, her mother is the
lady of the house, Lady Capulet.
Her daughter is a visage of beauty,
and intelligent, too!
How fortunate I am to have nursed her!
She is a visage of beauty, and...
I messed up!
Oh, no, I'm gonna cry!
It doesn't matter if we mess up.
Just keep going until the end.
Oh, my goodness!
I felt those qualities of such importance,
I said them twice!
Nice save.
My! Come hither, nurse!
Where goeth yonder gentleman?
The man with visage radiant as the sun!
I can tell she's had experience
being on a big stage before.
--There, him now who is going out of door!
--But boy, this Juliet...
...is so not in love.
--Go ask his name, if he be married...
--Still, she keeps looking at me.
And not how Hoshino was.
--My only love, sprung from my only hate.
--Hold on, Narata...
Are you performing for
an audience of one?
Okay, next up, our Kouka misfit,
Sarasa Watanabe.
"Group E Roles"
Okay, next up, our Kouka misfit,
Sarasa Watanabe.
That voice, is that Romeo?
Romeo, of house Montague?!
How dare the man come hither,
to the Capulet mansion itself!
She's directing her gaze
at the balcony seats.
And she's keeping her eyes at a 45-degree
angle so the lights will catch them.
Impressive.
Fetch me my rapier, boy!
That Romeo...
...is naught but a villain.
Sarasa Watanabe was reborn overnight.
And because today, she has an audience,
it's even more--
Okay! Good job, Group E.
Here's a question for you.
Who did you imagine as your audience?
The people in this room right now.
I-I didn't think about it.
A full house with balcony seats!
One person.
So that's why you were
staring at me that whole time?
Yes.
In JPX, they told us that even if
we only had an audience of one,
we should direct our performance
towards them and give it our all.
That's a good thought,
but the Kouka theater holds 2,500 people,
and every performance is a full house.
When you're acting, you should act
for every one of those 2,500 people!
Got it!
Also, Narata, if you're going to play
a musume-yaku, try to be a little sweeter.
This is the first time I've seen
a Juliet who didn't smile.
Next, Chika Sawada!
Yes, sir!
Great recovery after
you flubbed your line there.
But hunching over doesn't
make you an old woman.
Use that imagination.
Yes, sir.
Next up, Hoshino.
Sir!
Don't let your mind stray
when you're performing.
Leave yourself behind
when you step on stage.
--Okay, next!
--Wait, is that it?
For now, yeah.
You haven't learned any skills yet,
so I want you to act
however you want for now.
Don't get too hung up on my critique.
Right, last up, Watanabe.
Yes, sir!
Your impression was uncanny.
I'll admit, I was shocked.
But I'm sorry, Watanabe,
you'll never be a top star.
If you don't change, you'll never be
a top star of the Kouka Revue.
"Act 7: The Hanamichi
and the Silver Bridge"