The Kouka Opera was
founded in the Taisho era
by Ooizumi Minoru, part of a group of
big-name companies in Kobe.
It was an opera troupe
comprised entirely of unmarried women.
"The Rose of Versailles"
They quickly stole the hearts of thousands.
Their Male Lead actresses,
were said to be more
gentlemanly than 'real' men,
and earned them lots of female fans.
Years later, they established a school
to train the troupe's next big stars,
the Kouka School of
Musical and Theatrical Arts.
Its admittance rate is said to be
as low as Tokyo University,
with only the most beautiful and
talented actresses offered admission.
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone right now
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"Beneath the Cherry Tree,
in a Rain of Petals"
Excuse me, are you...
Naracchi?
Aren't you former member of JPX, Naracchi?
Oh, did I bother you?
I'm just such a huge Naracchi stan!
I'm so sorry they made you
graduate like that,
but I really hope you'll
keep giving it your all!
I'll stan you forever, Naracchi!
Good luck!
No! I'm scared! Someone, help!
Ai?
Taichi!
Ai? What happened?
An ex-fan touched my shoulder.
Oh.
Don't worry, he didn't follow you.
Here. This showed up at my sister's place.
It's your results from the first round
of Kouka admissions.
"Congratulations! You've passed
the first round of admissions!"
What does it say?
I made it through.
If I pass the second round,
I'll have two whole years without men.
There are teachers at school, too.
Male teachers, with me being one of them.
You're different, Taichi.
I know. C'mon, let's go home.
"Watanabe Tatami"
I hear Sarasa made it past
the first round for Kouka!
That's impressive.
Kouka's that acting troupe, right?
Where they do all that
singing and dancing?
As expected of her! Apple doesn't
fall far from the tree, after all.
Honey! Don't go mentioning that
in front of Grandpa Ken, now!
Why not?
Kouka and kabuki both start with K,
but they ain't the same!
Idiot!
That don't make it all right!
Grandpa Ken doesn't want to
hear any of those actin' words!
You don't get it!
Huh? What's this ruckus about?
Grandpa Ken! We heard Sarasa
got past the first round for Kouka!
Congratulations!
Is that why you're all here,
to celebrate? Well, thanks!
Why don't y'all come in?
Hey, Sarasa!
I don't think Sarasa's here.
She's not? Sarasa!
"Kouka School of Musical and
Theatrical Arts Admissions Department"
Don't worry about me, Grandma.
"Watanabe Family"
I was lucky enough to be born a girl,
so I'm gonna give it everything I've got!
Kouka School of Musical and Theatrical Arts,
"KSMTA Second Round Auditions"
reaches its centennial year,
and here we have the hopeful applicants
for its historic hundredth class.
How many applicants did we get this year?
1,135 applicants from all over Japan.
These girls are the top 200 who passed the first round.
Pretty crazy, huh?
Only 40 will be offered admission.
And they're all here an hour early. Good for them!
And if they pass, a nightmarish hierarchical society awaits them.
There's Ms. Hakuho Miyuki, former Female Lead in the Flower Troupe.
That'll be her daughter,
then: Hoshino Kaoru.
She'll make third generation Kouka student if she passes.
She has been flunking
the second round for past two years.
Proving yourself to be a
thoroughbred Kouka actress is tough.
She can hear us up here, y'know.
Did you see that intense glare?
Look, there's Sugimoto Sawa.
She's the Kouka Opera nerd
who aced the first round.
Yep. She's won awards performing in
her internationally famous ballet troupe.
Ditching prima ballerina for
Kouka actress, then? What a weirdo.
Whoa, what the heck?
There's two of the same girl.
They're twins, right?
Oh, is that right?
I was wondering why the same girl
was taking the test twice.
Let's get serious now, Mr. Narata.
S-Sorry! Excuse me.
She's a super ordinary girl.
Specializing in 'ordinary'.
Also, I don't see her.
Oh, her. The one you wouldn't
think was an applicant.
Yep. Super out of the ordinary.
Bet she didn't cross the first round.
Look, that's Narata Ai, ex-JPX idol!
Whatever.
She got canceled online
after she told a fan he was
"creepy" straight to his face.
That's why they made her 'graduate' early.
Whatever.
And now she's going
for Kouka? That feels wrong.
Whatever.
I don't care what anyone says about me.
"Applicant Ticket: Narata Ai"
I've trained myself not to feel anything
for a long time now.
I'm fine.
Your niece seems fascinated by
the Kouka cherry tree.
What?!
No! Get away from that tree, Ai!
You didn't tell her about its curse?
It's beautiful.
Are you alone, too?
How is it that you have such beauty,
yet no one wants to bask in it?
Excuse me!
Can I get a picture?!
Her arms and legs were long and lithe,
like a graceful gazelle.
Her eyes were sparkling and full of stars.
And she was so terrifyingly...
Hello! I'm Watanabe Sarasa, and I'm 15!
You're tall.
Yes?
Is that your applicant ticket?
I'll get it for you!
Huh?!
She floated!
No, she jumped without using her knees,
straight up, from a standing position!
She landed in the exact same place, too.
Her core strength must be insane!
Here you go!
You can thank me by
taking my picture! Here.
Huh? What?
Oh, the camera's this app here.
Wait, I'm-- I'm taking a picture? Of you?
Yeah! I wanna get
the cherry tree behind me.
Grandpa Ken had work today,
so he couldn't come,
but I wanna show him pictures later!
I can't believe it. How do they not know?
"If you stand beneath the Kouka
cherry tree before you're admitted,
you will never, ever,
be a Kouka top star."
Take one from this angle next!
Huh?
Now do one from over here!
Another?
This was how I, Narata Ai,
met Watanabe Sarasa.
Congrats for making it into Kouka!
How did she make it in?
Wait, who?
Sarasa. Something Sarasa.
And now, we present admitted applicants
for the 100th class of the Kouka School for Musical and Theatrical Arts!
"Admitted Students"
Of course I got in.
A rotten fish is still a fish.
But how did she get in?
Congratulations to all successful applicants.
I'm Vice Principal Oizumi Haruhiko.
Let's talk about your
next steps after admission.
Everyone's avoiding me.
They won't even sit next to me.
I'm so sorry! My phone call
with Grandpa Ken took forever!
Can I sit next to you?
Why would you intentionally sit
next to me? And even yell about it?!
Oh, you were near the cherry tree the other day!
The cherry tree?
I see you got admitted as well!
She didn't recognize Naracchi?
Here I thought everyone knew the JPX48.
Maybe she doesn't have a TV.
Or maybe...
She's doing it on purpose!
She's gonna hear you!
I totally forgot to
ask your name back then!
What is it?
I hope we can be friends!
Excuse me, you two, please be quiet.
You two?!
How the hell did she get in?
Let me tell you, you're not rotten, Ai.
Also, it's interesting, you being curious about others.
That's not it though.
Watanabe Sarasa was admitted on
the recommendations of
Mr. Andou, the acting teacher;
and Mr. Ohki, the history teacher.
She's not what we'd usually admit, sure.
But this is our centennial year!
So how about we get a little daring?
She barely knows any ballet, and her
singing voice is hardly Kouka material,
but between her incredible height
and her utter fearlessness,
we might be able to make her into a star!
Number 0251, Watanabe Sarasa!
Thanks for having me today!
Her fearlessness?
"Get daring" and
"make her a star"?
Hey, don't play with your food.
She's from Asakusa and
lives with her grandfather.
She wasn't born in the lap of luxury.
"SUBJ: I'm in Kobe"
"Hey, mom, I know you probably
don't care, but I got into Kouka."
"SUBJ: I'm in Kobe"
"Hey, mom"
She went on about how she "had to get
back to Asakusa," but kept stopping...
Oh, it's from Keiko this time.
"I got into Kouka!"
"Headed home on the bullet train soon!"
Ooh, Sho!
"I got into Kouka!"
"Headed home on the bullet train soon!"
And sent!
Wait, I forgot Takubo!
"I got into Kouka!"
Oh, wait...
What a moron.
Why didn't she just send a group text?
"SUBJ: I'm in Kobe"
"Hey, mom"
Just admitted, huh? What's your name?
Narata Ai.
Oh, I think I saw you on TV--
Right, I shouldn't mention
any of that. Sorry, honey.
First-year students are on the third
and fourth floors of Dorm #2.
You'll be in a double in room 302.
Thank you, ma'am.
There's no stench of men. I love it.
Today I begin my nice, relaxing life.
Oh! You're the one from the cherry tree!
"Narata Ai"
"Watanabe Sarasa"
I'd like you to change my room.
You can't, Miss Narata.
Nobody gets special treatment here.
I totally thought they'd
separate us 'cause we're twins.
Isn't this awesome, Chiaki?!
We're gonna be together
forever and ever, Chika!
Yeah! Together forever, Chiaki!
I see, even though your mom
and grandma were Female Leads,
you want to be a Male Lead, Hoshino?
You also want to be a
Male Lead right, Sugimoto?
That's right. The biggest Kouka stars
are their top Male Leads.
We might end up as rivals someday.
Let me tell you this right now,
I won't give in easy.
I'll keep that in mind.
They're scary...
Hey, you're back!
What's all that?
I bought these from hardware store.
I just really need my privacy.
Wow, you're so handy, dear Ai!
Dear Ai?
I read your name off the card
on the door! Narata Ai, right?
Can I call you Ai?
Don't violate my border!
Violate your what?
Stay on your side!
I'm too tall to stretch out on my side!
Then don't stretch out on the floor!
I just vacuumed it, so it's all clean!
Why don't you join me?
It feels really nice!
H-Hey!
The next day, we started our preliminary
week of classes: Guidance Week.
On the final day, disaster struck.
What? But I'm here at the usual time!
We told you that we'd be meeting
a half hour early today.
Come now, fall in line.
What a mean trick to pull on the last day!
You should've woken me up, Ai!
I'm Captain Anai from
the Itami Military Base Security Force.
Ballet, modern dance, vocals,
traditional dance, classical theater.
To everyone who spent this Guidance Week
practicing these artistic disciplines,
I'll be teaching you how to move
and act in synchrony.
Wow, the JSDF is here?
What's he mean by "synchrony"?
In theater terms, we'd say
stage awareness, or moving in sync.
You girls! No chit-chat!
First, form four groups of ten!
And, start marching in order at once!
Line up!
One! Two! One! Two!
I love having Captain Anai every year.
He's such a character.
I love him, too.
He's getting quite passionate
about this group of girls.
Usually he leaves at lunch,
but he's still here.
Likely because there's that one group
that can't seem to get it right.
And our first-year student policy is
if one group stays, everyone stays.
Oh, there's Naracchi! She's so cute!
You sure love your JPX, huh, Hijiri?
What're you guys doing here?
Scoping out the first years for later?
No, we're here to
cheer them on, Mr. Andou!
Halt!
One more time! Forward march!
Left, right, one, two!
One, two! One, two!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
Halt!
Something's just not right.
You, you,
you, and you.
Line up and give it a go.
Salute!
At ease!
Attention!
Arm right, and out!
I see.
You.
Y-Yes, sir!
You're trying too hard to follow everyone.
You're always a second off.
Focus on yourselves more.
Yes, sir.
You.
Yes, sir!
You're a bit fast. Don't try to stand out.
Coorindation is essential in a group march.
But I was...
Now, you.
Your core's weak and
your posture's not straight.
I know you're coming from the idol world,
but here's not the place to be cutesy.
Give it your all!
I don't like being touched, sir.
I just don't get girls your age.
My daughter won't even let me hug her.
But everything's "sexual harassment" these days.
Exhausting, but us guys
gotta watch ourselves, too.
Right then, you're last.
Hot damn, you're tall.
And that's sexual harassment, sir!
It is? My apologies, then.
Right, then, you're tall. Your arms and
legs are long. You've got a big wingspan.
So you need to consider your surroundings
a second earlier than the rest.
Other than that, you're good!
Really? Yay, I got a perfect score!
Would it be all right if I
gave your shoulder a shove?
Sure, go ahead!
You've got strong legs and a good core,
just as I expected. I'm impressed!
Now, let's put that critique
to work and try that again!
Hold on, sir!
That wasn't fair. I wasn't ready!
I won't move an inch from this spot!
Incredible!
Would you like to join the JSDF, miss?
He's "miss"-ing her now?!
Nope! I'm gonna join the Kouka Opera
and play Lady Oscar!
Did you hear that?
Sure did.
This is kinda scary...
Hey, Watanabe! You know
what that means, right?
It means you're aiming to be
one of the Kouka Opera's top stars!
Oh, is that so?
Then sure, I'll do that!
I'll be a top star!
There are four troupes:
Spring, Summer, Autumn, and Winter.
Out of 320 actresses, only one from
each troupe gets to be its top star.
Only four actresses earn that honor.
Well, all right.
I don't care.
I don't care about those at all.
Ai! Where are you?
Let's walk back to the dorm together, Ai!
Ai?
She's not here, either.
What is this, a horror movie?
What was that weird pose
Watanabe did back there?
A kickboxing move?
Maybe it was capoeira,
or some martial art move?
It was a fumidashi.
Wait, Ms. Kirishima,
you mean like in sumo wrestling?
No. It's a special move that Sukeroku
does in his deha entrance.
Sukeroku's deha?
It's from a kabuki play.
Kabuki?
"Ex-JPX star Ai Narata
accepted to Kouka School!"
I finally found you.
I finally found you, Ai!
Let's walk back together!
Sheesh, where were you?
I was looking all over for you!
"Act 2: Those Who Long to
Cross the Silver Bridge"