Sarasa.
I have superpowers and
can read your mind right now.
Can I say something to help you?
Even if you can't walk down
the kabuki hanamichi anymore...
...we can walk down
the Kouka silver bridge.
How's that sound?
Great!
Everyone dreams of becoming a superstar at least once
So that you can make the world envious
1, 2, 3, quick like Allegro
Hold that hand and come
Let's build a rainbow together at Andante
You aren't anyone yet
So any of your future can come true
Your dream is just beginning
Little by little, you can become yourself
Tomorrow's gonna blow another wind
So dream as many times as you want
Someday, become the stage's sparkling star
so that the spotlight shines upon you
"Kaoru's Summer"
The students at the Kouka School
of Musical and Theatrical Arts
return to campus, refreshed from
their summer vacation,
and began to ready themselves
for a new semester.
It's so much hotter down here!
You guys went up north to Hokkaido, right?
Yeah, summers there are super cool.
I saw two of the Spring Troupe's shows!
I have to say, Ryuu Asahina's performance
in the final show was transcendent!
Whoa, Hoshino-san!
You cut your hair!
It was hot long.
Oh, wow!
You've got such great hair,
so of course it'd look good short!
I do want to be an otoko-yaku,
so I figured now's the time to cut it.
You're so cool! You look so handsome!
C'mon, guys, literally everyone
cuts their hair!
She's embarrassed.
Kaoru's embarrassed.
You're totally embarrassed!
Whatever! What the hell is
wrong with you and Naracchi?!
I keep telling you to
start acting like pros!
Pros don't let themselves
get suntanned like that!
What kind of reaction is that?!
And don't act like you're
not in trouble, too, Naracchi!
I was just having so much fun,
I didn't realize I was getting tan.
That doesn't matter! Fine Kouka ladies
do not let themselves get a tan!
Eek.
Kaoru does go all-out.
Why does Hoshino always
walk around with an umbrella?
Who knows?
A teacher told her to lose the umbrella,
but she argued there's
no school rule against them!
Apparently she wants to be an actress or
something? So she doesn't want to get tan.
So then I posted it!
"Shin-Nase
for Zushi Station"
You didn't!
Whoa, look over there.
He's on our baseball team.
Huh?
Y'know, he's related to
that hot major leaguer.
Really? He's like, not even hot though.
You think we'll finally
make it to Koshien this year?
Ugh, look at her!
A school uniform and an umbrella?
Who does she think she is?
Oh, she went to my middle school.
Apparently she wants to go to
the Kouka theater school,
but she still hasn't gotten in yet.
We live near the sea.
The sun shines bright, especially during
these hot summer months.
I can do what I can
to keep from getting tan,
but there's not much I can do
about the heat.
"Shizuka Hoshino"
I'm so glad you're
feeling better, Mari-chan!
I was so scared when I heard
you were in the hospital!
Come on in.
How are you feeling, Grandma?
Oh, Kaoru-chan! How nice of you to visit!
My grandmother was a top musume-yaku
of the Kouka Acting Troupe.
They called her
"Spring's Lovely Snow White."
Even now, she's still surrounded by fans.
My goodness, is this her?
Yes, my granddaughter.
Oh, my! It's nice to meet you!
She's a senior in high school now.
Is she? Then that means...
She must be breaking from tradition and
won't be joining the Kouka troupe, then?
This is her last year to apply, so she's
giving it all she's got right now.
My, is that right!
We're rooting for you, hon! Break a leg!
Your kidney stone surgery
must have been so scary.
Though with how you sparkle,
I'm sure they pulled out a diamond!
Everyone must be so disappointed.
After all, I hardly look the part.
Semester's finally over!
Let's hit karaoke on the way home!
I'm going on a date with my boyfriend.
What are you up to, Kaoru?
I've got lessons every day from now on.
Wait, really?
Kaoru's so weird.
I want to be an otoko-yaku!
A cool, handsome actress
who plays male roles!
"Yukiko Hoshino"
Sorry, I was in the middle of class.
Could you stop by the hospital
on your way home?
Grandma mentioned a book
she wanted us to pick up for her.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, thanks!
H-Hey, uh.
I heard some girls the other day say you
were trying out for some acting troupe.
And, uh, my grandma's
a big fan of that troupe,
so she told me to ask you some questions.
Like what?
Like... what's your name?
Ugh, what am I even saying...
Excuse me!
Are you Tsuji-san from South High?
Uh, yeah?
Good luck in the Koshien prelims.
Also, could you give this
to your brother Kaito?!
I really, really like him.
Whenever I feel down, I just watch
him play, and it makes me feel better.
I know he's headed off
to the major leagues,
and he's engaged
to that model, Seira-chan,
but I'd really appreciate it
if you'd give him my letter!
I don't want any part in that.
I'm not my brother's keeper.
B-But--
The school and my brother
don't want people doing this.
I'm sorry!
You okay?
Please don't cry.
Hoshino.
That's my name.
Kaoru Hoshino. What's yours?
Rikuto Tsuji.
The Kouka School of
Musical and Theatrical Arts?
Yep.
What do they teach you there?
Everything from proper manners
to singing and ballet.
We do a lot of physical training.
Damn!
Right? I gotta be able to lift
those musume-yaku girls!
Musume what?
The troupe's all-female, so they sort
actresses into male or female roles.
Are you gonna have to wear a moustache?
Yeah! The guys in my class
make fun of that all the time.
Oh, I didn't mean to
make fun of it! I was just surprised.
I've seen your brother on TV a few times.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, figures.
That's not what I meant.
My mom and grandma
were both in the Kouka troupe,
and my grandma was pretty famous.
I was just thinking how
we have that in common.
Rikuto's on the South High
Varsity Baseball Team,
and every year, they make it to
at least the Koshien prelim finals.
But Rikuto usually ends up
warming the bench.
Tsuji's gotten a hell of
a lot better all of the sudden.
He's got the skill, that's for sure.
He just gets into his head too much.
Hey, guys, come eat!
Here! I made this one for you.
Thanks.
We're graduating this year, so you better
make it to Koshien this time!
Good point. Not like I'll
get to play, though.
Oh, c'mon! Your brother's going to
the major leagues! You can do it!
I never get bothered when
people try to compare me to them!
Just 'cause we're related doesn't mean
we're the same! I'm me!
Wow.
You're so strong.
You have a hard time
expressing yourself when you sing.
Give it more feeling and
enunciate those syllables.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry! You'll be a great singer.
Your mother and grandmother
were both great singers.
I'm me.
That's what I keep telling myself.
♬ Falling from the sky ♬
♬ Like white snow, but warm, ♬
♬ Like a spring fairy ♬
♬ Fluttering down ♬
"When are you visiting your grandma next?"
Huh?
The sun's really bright today.
Oh, yeah, you've gotta
watch out for that, huh.
I'm super tan, like Othello.
In the center of the Kouka stage,
there's this part of the apron
called the silver bridge.
Only a few stars get to walk across it.
The big stars, huh?
I'm gonna be a top otoko-yaku
and walk across that silver bridge.
You know those people who say "I'm getting
in!" when there's no guarantee they will,
then end up getting in?
Yeah?
I'll be honest, I wish I had their guts.
I could never say that. I know better than
anyone just how hard it is to get in.
When are you going to
see your grandma again?
You sure have been coming to see me a lot!
Y-You think so?
How many guys are on a baseball team?
Nine. You hear the English number
used a lot, right?
I don't know anything about baseball.
You do spend all your time taking lessons.
I can't come to watch,
but I hope you guys win.
I'll have to wear more manly fashions
when I get into the troupe,
so I'm wearing all the skirts
I can right now.
Y'know, Hoshino-san,
I bet that even with a moustache,
you'd still look pretty.
What the hell?
Oh my God. Oh my God.
He didn't. Oh, geez.
I've never gotten called pretty by a boy.
"We won our first game!"
"Nice!"
"I warmed the bench lmao"
C'mere, girls! We've got
a veteran joining us today!
Ta-dah! Here's an admittee
from our dance school,
second-year Kouka student Yamagishi-san!
She'll be using our studio to practice
over her summer break.
Thank you for having me!
Kaoru-chan!
I'm so glad you're still
trying to get into Kouka!
Yeah, this year's my last chance.
Oh, wow. Let me know
if I can help you at all!
You helped me a lot when
I was trying to get in, after all!
Hey, what's up with Yamagishi-san?
Yeah, she's kind of a ditz.
She always went on and on about how
she was gonna be the 'next top star.'
She was good friends with Kaoru,
but then she got in right after
ninth grade, on her first try!
Wow. And Hoshino-san's
on her fourth try now.
Guess having connections
doesn't help you get in.
You've gotta have the talent.
"I warmed the bench lmao"
"There's a fireworks festival tonight.
Wanna go with me?"
My, you're here again!
Am I coming too often?
Not at all. I love when
you come to visit me, Kaoru-chan.
I'll be out of the hospital soon, anyway.
How are your lessons going?
Good. I'm taking eight lessons
a week right now.
My, there aren't even
that many days in the week!
It's wonderful how you young ones
can work so hard and still shine bright.
But I worry about you.
You're such a sweet girl. I don't want you
to push yourself too hard.
If there's something else
you'd like to do,
you're welcome to do that instead.
If there's another life
you'd like to live,
you can always start
down a different path.
I know.
You look normal.
Normal?
I mean, you're not
covering up or anything.
Well, the sun's not out.
This is the first time we've hung out
somewhere other than the bus stop.
You look good in your yukata.
C'mon, big bro!
Hold on!
We're gonna miss it!
Wanna walk?
Yeah.
Hungry? We've got piping hot okonomiyaki!
So you're winning all your games!
Oh, yeah.
You've won four now?
Yeah.
Wow.
And it's cool that you're hanging out
instead of practicing right now?
Yeah.
Hey, what's got you so down?
I've been doing really well recently,
but I still haven't gotten a chance
to play in any games.
Makes me wonder, what's the point
in trying so hard at baseball?
I grew up playing baseball
with my older brother.
And since my brother's so talented,
everyone expects me to be good at it, too.
I figured I had to live up
to those expectations,
so I joined the baseball team
without a second thought.
But I keep wondering if I'm wasting
my time forcing myself to do all this.
I bet you feel that way
all the time, too, huh?
Why does everyone always assume that?
I don't. I never do.
Sure, the pressure gets to me sometimes,
but this is something I want to do!
I've never forced myself to do this,
not for a second!
This is the path I chose! I want this!
And I'm not giving up until the very end!
I'll do whatever it takes
to get into the Kouka School!
I-I'm sorry, I--
Don't assume I'm like you.
Bye.
I'm so stupid.
For a split second, I felt jealous
of the typical high school girl's life.
Going to karaoke,
going on dates, holding hands.
Having a boy worry about me
and try to cheer me up.
♬ Falling from the sky ♬
♬ Like white snow, but warm, ♬
♬ Like a spring fairy ♬
♬ Fluttering down ♬
♬ Ah, the Kouka cherry blossoms ♬
♬ Falling upon the earth,
becoming one with the ground, ♬
--♬ to become new life, and go to you ♬
--I'm going to make it.
♬ Now, they flutter and dance ♬
I swear...
I swear I will!
"Rikuto Tsuji"
"BLOCK"
It's between South High and Hama-Dai
for the finals this year again, eh?
South High's down by one in the ninth.
"HAMA HIGH: 3"
"SOUTH HIGH: 2"
South High's down by one in the ninth.
"HAMA HIGH: 3"
"SOUTH HIGH: 2"
Think they're gonna lose
the final again this year?
--They still got
the bottom of the ninth...
--Pinch hitting for
Number 9's Shimada-kun,
Tsuji-kun, Number 11!
Focus! Focus!
C'mon, Tsuji!
You can do it! Hit it out of the park!
Hey, kid! We're missing everything!
It's outta here!
--Did they win?
--That home run clinches the win!
--Yeah, they won! They won!
--What a way to end a game!
Whoa, are those tears?
--Aww, you're cryin' tears of joy!
--South High advances to Koshien!
South High went to Koshien but
was eliminated after their first game.
"Koshien Stadium"
South High went to Koshien but
was eliminated after their first game.
My grandma was discharged
from the hospital,
and I never went to that bus stop again.
And now...
Hey, Sarasa? Could you not
make gross noises?
You're from Kanagawa, right, Hoshino-san?
Did you hear about this?
It's getting tons of RTs right now!
Someone put this letter up
at this bus stop by the sea!
Please leave this note up for this summer.
To K: I'm still playing baseball.
Thank you for everything.
Nobody knows if it's for a boy or a girl,
or how old they are!
Isn't that romantic, though?!
Yeah.
One day, when I walk across
that silver bridge,
and you're still playing baseball,
maybe I'll save you
a primo seat in the SS section.
Maybe I'll even tell you...
...that I was in love with you.
If roses had no thorns and were easier to pick,
it would stop being a rose, for it would be a false flower
Is it the fate of a rose to bloom with thorns?
Is it the fate of a person, too,
to be born with something predetermined?
Could someone tell me?
The path I walk is already already paved
Were the Goddess of Fate by my side,
I'd like my path be filled with rainbow-colored flowers
Please make that wish of mine come true
"Act 9: The Two Juliets"